{"prompt": "So I have really gotten into modding GTA IV. I have installed LCPDFR, multiple Plugins, ENB's", "expected": ", etc. But I am having one issue that I cannot resolve. I loaded in a Unmarked CVPI that supports", "actual": ", BSP Mod, MPT, and a lot more.\n\nI have managed to get the \"Buster\" theme installed. I think it's the default one, but it's so cool!\n\nWhen I was reading through the GTA IV BSP, I noticed that there are a couple of files in the Data folder that I wasn't aware of.\n\nFirst, there is the \"Buster\".bin file.\n\nThen there is a \"Buster\" .xml file. That's what is making the \"Buster\" theme so cool. (Not to be confused with \"B"}
{"prompt": "\"\n\nWe will work closely with you and try our best to resolve any issues. We're here to help! We", "expected": " will get back to you promptly.\n\n\"\n\n\n\n\n\nItem description", "actual": " will assist you to get information or to ask questions. We will also provide you the most professional and affordable service to remove all types of furniture, upholstery, and/or mattresses from your home.\n\nWe are able to help you find the way to the same day service, because we have the most professional, experienced, and knowledgeable staff to assist you.\n\nContact us now!\n\nWe at StairMaster, have made our services available to those who want to save time and money by getting all of their furniture removed from their apartment or house. We offer same-day carpet and sofa removal"}
{"prompt": "Stefania roraimae\n\nStefania roraimae (common names: Roraima tree", "expected": "frog, Roraima stefania) is a species of frog in the family Hemiphractidae. It is", "actual": "frog, Roraima treefrog, Roraima treefrog frog, Roraima treefrog/treefrog frog, Roraima treefrog-e-a, Roriama treefrog/treefrog; also known as Roriama) is a species of tree frog native to the Andes, eastern slopes of the Andes and the Guadalquivir valley of southern Spain and southern France. It is found in a narrow belt from the Andes to Sierra Nevada de Santa Marta, a belt of mountains in east-central Andalusia.\n\nStructure\nSte"}
{"prompt": "Abdullahi Bayero\n\nAbdullahi Bayero dan Muhammad Abbas (1881–1953) was Sarki", "expected": " (Emir) of Kano, with headquarters in Kano, Kano State, Nigeria from 1926 to 1953. ", "actual": " (Chief of Police) of the Malayan police. He was one of the most experienced detectives of the era, and a famous detective who was called a \"walking encyclopedia\".\n\nEarly life and education\nBayero was born in 1896. Born to a small family in the town of Maman, Pahang, British Malaya, Bayero was one of eight children. His father died in 1905 whilst giving him education, and he moved to Istana Utara, where he joined the Police. Bayero began his education at the Madrasa Khayasul, now Madrasa Sains"}
{"prompt": "Winter break for law students is a glorious time of year. Of course we still have to deal with our usual ‘pro", "expected": "blems’ such as being poor, not having any time, and all of the other over dramatized first world problems", "actual": "blems’ such as exams and essays, but it’s a chance to re-evaluate your life and plan your summer. It’s also a time for making new friends, and a chance to indulge in socialising and fun. But there is a downside - you need to be careful what you talk to your friends about. This is because, in addition to all those problems, and potential distractions such as the examiners, there are a number of legal myths that go around this time of year. Here are just ten more:\n\n1. There are legal myths about the summer holidays.\n\n"}
{"prompt": "Preschool Activities on the Life Cycle of a Frog\n\nIn this thematic lesson we are giving children a first hand visual", "expected": " experience of the life cycle of a frog. Bring a tank into class to have student watch tadpoles develop into frogs!", "actual": " experience of the life cycle of a frog. We are doing this with the help of a life size frog that we are using as a model. We have found that the use of this life size frog is very effective for introducing the topic and making the information very accessible for all age groups. I hope you enjoy the project! I have provided a sample of the craft and all materials that you will need. This project has been designed for children aged 5 to 8 years.\n\nCraft Materials\n\nFrosted snow.\n\nScissors.\n\nGlue.\n\nGlitter glue.\n\nPaint"}
{"prompt": "1. Introduction {#sec1-sensors-20-00894}\n===============\n\nThe usage", "expected": " of wide-angle camera lenses in vision-based applications demands greater precision in terms of image projection geometry such as distortion compensation and", "actual": " of radar technology has been limited to a few select countries due to its complexity and cost. However, the use of radar has also been expanded in order to avoid the need for manned or manned-operated aircraft. This is also due to the fact that the radar can perform various tasks under various conditions. Furthermore, the radar also uses radar technology, which can be used for various applications. These applications cover a range of activities including military uses, commercial, infrastructure, and transportation.\n\nThe most common radar technology used for these applications is the radar altimeter. This technology is based on the use of a radar wave that is"}
{"prompt": "Our new issue, “After Bernie,” is out now. Our questions are simple: what did Bernie accomplish,", "expected": " why did he fail, what is his legacy, and how should we continue the struggle for democratic socialism? Get a discounted print", "actual": " why did he fail, what is his legacy, and how should we continue the struggle for democratic socialism? Get a discounted print subscription today !\n\nThe world has changed profoundly since the late 1960s: a world where the United States emerged as the sole superpower and a world in which the socialist countries of Latin America suffered a series of defeats during the 1980s, the “lost generation” of Latin American Marxists left the continent in the 1990s, and the United States turned its attentions to domestic problems. But the Latin American left, for the most part, has not followed the lead of the working class"}
{"prompt": "package rocks.inspectit.ui.rcp.editor.table.input;\n\nimport java.lang.", "expected": "reflect.InvocationTargetException;\nimport java.util.ArrayList;\nimport java.util.Collections;", "actual": "annotation.Annotation;\nimport java.util.Collection;\nimport java.util.Collections;\nimport java.util.HashSet;\nimport java.util.LinkedHashMap;\nimport java.util.List;\nimport java.util.Map;\nimport java.util.Set;\n\nimport org.eclipse.core.runtime.Plugin;\nimport org.eclipse.ui.IEditorPart;\nimport org.eclipse.ui.IWorkbenchActionDelegate;\nimport org.eclipse.ui.IWorkbenchWindow;\n"}
{"prompt": "Crazy Stupid Groban\n\nA killer role in the new Steve Carell flick has forced our brains to process this shocking", "expected": " truth: Josh Groban = damn funny\n\nJosh Groban always seemed like a guy we would ignorantly lump in the", "actual": " news: The comedy star is actually a serial killer.\n\nThe news was revealed in a new interview with The New York Times, which first reported the story yesterday. In the nearly one-hour conversation, Carell says he has been in therapy for an unspecified number of years and that he fears he is “unhinged.”\n\n\n\nSteve Carell, Actor, Actor of the Year, R-rated Movie Star, and Serial Killer of the Year\n\nIt’s just the latest in Carell’s storied and, at times, tragic Hollywood career. This much is"}
{"prompt": "First Findings in the Route of the Maize Bushy Stunt Phytoplasma Within Its Vector Dalbulus", "expected": " maidis (Hemiptera: Cicadellidae).\nIn the pathosystem of Dalbulus madis", "actual": " auratus (Cyprinidae) in South Africa\n\nBy\n\nKieran Fergal\n\nDirector\n\nDepartment of Animal and Veterinary Sciences\n\nUniversity of KwaZulu-Natal\n\nPretoria, South Africa\n\nKeywords\n\nAphthous stomatitis virus\n\nAphthous stomatitis virus\n\nMaize bushy stunt phytoplasma\n\nMaize bushy stunt phytoplasma\n\nMaize bushy stunt phytoplasma\n\nDepartment of Animal and Veterinary Sciences\n\nUniversity"}
{"prompt": "Apr 5, 2012; St. Paul, MN, USA; Minnesota Wild defenseman Tom Gilbert (77) during the second period", "expected": " against the Chicago Blackhawks at the Xcel Energy Center. The Wild defeated the Blackhawks 2-1 in a shootout. Brace", "actual": " against the Minnesota Wild in the second round of NHL hockey in St. Paul, Minnesota, USA. Mandatory Credit: Brad Rempel-USA TODAY Sports\n\nMINNESOTA WILD (40-27-11, 78 points) vs. D.C. CHOKEHON (21-25-12, 35 points)\n\nWith the Wild trailing by six and down 3-0 with just 2:31 to play in the third period, the Washington Capitals were able tie the game.\n\nAfter the game, they were able to score twice more to win it, 6-5.\n\nIn"}
{"prompt": "Stimulation of pepsinogen release from chief cells by Helicobacter pylori: evidence for a role of", "expected": " calcium and calmodulin.\nTo define the mechanisms by which Helicobacter pylori stimulates pepsinogen secretion", "actual": " guanine nucleotide regulatory proteins or the guanine nucleotide-binding regulatory protein-like protein.\nWe examined the ability of the Helicobacter pylori-induced stimulation of the major secretory isoform of pepsinogen (pHPG), the secretion of which is induced by H. pylori, to stimulate pepsinogen release in cultured rat chief cells. We used pepsinogen expression in cultured chief cells as an index of H. pylori-induced secretion for the following reasons: (1) H. pylori-induced stimulation of pHPG secretion is"}
{"prompt": "Propagation characteristics of planar segmented waveguides with parabolic index segments.\nWe have analyzed the linear propagation", "expected": " characteristics of planar periodic segmented waveguides with infinitely extended parabolic refractive-index segments in the transverse direction", "actual": " of a narrow linewidth optical beam through a planar segmented waveguide with parabolic index segments. The beam is initially focused at the input end of the waveguide by a lens on the order of the width of the cross section of the waveguide. Upon propagation through the waveguide, the wavefront spreads, but the intensity of the beam remains constant. The propagation characteristics of the beam depend on the relative location of the input and output ends of the waveguide with respect to the longitudinal axes of the segments of the waveguide. We obtain the phase front for arbitrary input and output points on the optical axis by"}
{"prompt": "勤労統計問題の原因は「COB", "expected": "OLプログラムのバグ」\n\n厚生労働省の毎", "actual": "LL」というエコノミスト向けの問題などだ。\n\nCOBLLが抱える問題は、「コミュニケーション基盤が破棄するか、欧州諸国で広く使われている技術です」という。欧州では、コミュニケーション能�"}
{"prompt": "Wireless Local Area Networks (WLANs) include multiple wireless communication devices that communicate over one or more wireless channels. When", "expected": " operating in an infrastructure mode, a wireless communication device called an access point (AP) provides connectivity with a network such as the", "actual": " an access point covers a large area, there is a desire to broadcast information in various data formats from multiple sources. The wireless communication devices are capable of receiving the data from the access point and displaying graphics associated with the data such that the wireless communication devices are capable of receiving information from multiple wireless communication sources in a single wireless communication device.\nWLAN technologies have rapidly grown over the last decade. Wireless LAN technology is now being employed in a variety of environments. In general, wireless LAN technology is designed to work within a licensed band. The licensed band is often divided into sub-bands, e.g., 14-14"}
{"prompt": "Fractures of the odontoid process. Conservative and operative treatment. Prognostic factors.\nIn a retrospective study", "expected": " 33 fractures of the dens were analyzed. Nonoperative treatment was successful in types I and III, but unsuccessful in 48.5", "actual": " the results of conservative and operative treatment in 30 patients with fractures of the odontoid process were analyzed and the findings compared to determine prognostic factors for outcome. Follow up time for the patients ranged from 1 month to 6 years (mean 52 months). The results of surgery were excellent or good in 91% of the cases: 11 were in-hospital deaths, 8 had neurologic complications (1 spinal cord ischemia, 2 meningitis, 2 subdural hematomas, 1 intracranial hematoma, 1 pneumonia, 1 cerebrospinal fluid fistula), and 1 experienced a delayed death"}
{"prompt": "How academic labs can approach the drug discovery process as a way to synergize with big pharma.\nWhile the pharmaceutical industry", "expected": " is facing highly challenging times, the academic drug discovery sector has the potential to contribute meaningfully to the discovery of novel drug targets", "actual": " continues to grow, and new drugs are developed, many times without being developed by universities, there are many scientists who are trying to find the most efficient way to do drug research. One of the keys to accomplishing this task is to take the approach to drug discovery that big pharma has made so successful -- creating a team of scientists that can work together efficiently. Big pharma has created this team by identifying and working with potential drug targets. While this strategy has worked very well, often the drug candidates are created with no knowledge of the target, or only a little. However, in many cases, a small amount of"}
{"prompt": "\n\nE-text prepared by Susan Carr, Turgut Dincer, Charlene Taylor, and the\nOnline", "expected": " Distributed Proofreading Team (http://www.pgdp.net) from page\nimages generously made available by Internet Archive", "actual": " Distributed Proofreading Team (http://www.pgdp.net)\n\n\n\nTranscriber's note:\n\n   Characters in bold are surrounded by =equal signs=, if any.\n\n   Minor typographical errors have been corrected without note.\n\n   A list of these changes is found at the end of this e-text file.\n\n\n\n\n\nJOHNNY DEAR\n\n\n\n\n\nJOHNNY DEAR\n\n\n\n\n\n[Illustration: \"There was a great, loud roar of applause, and\nevery one was glad that he had come out well"}
{"prompt": "Many varieties of waveguide filters are presently known involving periodic structures such a periodic corrugations. Such waveguides can be", "expected": " open or closed, involve ultrasound or electromagnetic waves and, if electromagnetic, can be light, microwave, millimeter or other ranges", "actual": " found in the art, for example, in:\n______________________________________ U.S. Pat. No. 4,939,851 3,926,788 4,831,961 4,841,768 4,910,955 4,811,829 4,900,096 British Patent GB Patent No. 1,078,734 4,831,961 514,841 515,841 Swiss Patent, No. 551,929 4,818,541 514,841 515,841 4"}
{"prompt": "The Washington Post: Why China is removing crosses from hundreds of churches\n\nA draft of official regulations relating to religious structures in", "expected": " the eastern Chinese province of Zhejiang was publicly released this week, offering a glimpse into the means by which local authorities seek", "actual": " China has been made public, and one of them proposes removing the religious symbols such as religious crosses normally used by Christians in order to “observe religious freedoms.”\n\nThe draft also states that “The government does not have any religious beliefs on Christians.”\n\nA total of 576 religious structures in 39 cities have been registered since this summer as part of a government initiative to regulate religious activity and put it on a “religion-inclusive” basis. Officials claim the proposed regulations would allow worship spaces not related to churches, mosques, or other religious organizations to “"}
{"prompt": "Learn how to create a WordPress theme using Pinegrow\n\n';\n\nWhat is the course about?\n\nThe course", "expected": " is about WordPress theme development using Pinegrow WP a desktop app for Windows, Mac and Linux that lets you build responsive websites faster", "actual": " will teach you how to build a WordPress theme from scratch with the latest version of WordPress, Pinegrow, and using advanced coding skills.\n\nWhat topics are covered in the course?\n\nThis course covers all the topics needed to create a new WordPress theme from scratch, from a blank theme file with only a title and menu options. We will cover how to get started and how to make sure that your theme has all the features needed to be successful. In the last part of the course you will learn exactly what each aspect of a WordPress theme should have in terms of both HTML and CSS.\n\nWhat are you"}
{"prompt": "DEFINED_PHASES=install postinst preinst prerm pretend\nDESCRIPTION=user for prometheus\n", "expected": "EAPI=7\nKEYWORDS=alpha amd64 arm arm64 hppa ia64 m68k ~m", "actual": "EAPI=7\nHOMEPAGE=https://github.com/defunkt/prometheus\nIUSE=doc\nKEYWORDS=~amd64 ~x86\nLICENSE=MIT\nRDEPEND=>=app-crypt/prometheus\nSLOT=0\nSRC_URI=https://github.com/defunkt/prometheus/archive/0.11.0.tar.gz -> prometheus-0.11.0.tar.gz\n_md5_=b0bb16eee9bdda25f8eba0af"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nWhat is \"Device: 802h/2050d\" stands for in inode?\n\nWhen", "expected": " I list an inode with stat command:\n  File: 'text'\n  Size: 0    ", "actual": " I search for \"device:802h_2050d\" in Linux, I get a bunch of results.\nFor example, for 2.6.18-358.22.1.el6.x86_64 I get\n$ file /lib/modules/2.6.18-358.22.1.el6.x86_64/kernel/net/wireless/ath/ath9k/ath9k-phy-core.ko\n/lib/modules/2.6.18-358.22.1.el6.x86_64/"}
{"prompt": "Manchester United were widely commended for their decision to freeze season ticket prices for a sixth consecutive year as well as slashing prices for", "expected": " young fans and EFL Cup matches.\n\nUtd's cheapest season ticket has not budged from £532,", "actual": " suites, junior club membership and match-day entrance and hospitality packages.\n\nIn the same week, Arsenal, West Ham United and Charlton Athletic also announced record low prices for season tickets, and West Bromwich Albion, Bournemouth and Liverpool announced the resumption of their former ticket pricing policies.\n\nAll four teams spent around £2.25bn on new players last summer, despite winning just two of their first 19 competitive games, with the average cost per game at around £6.75.\n\nUnited had a season ticket for more than £70 - a sum that was £45 above the club"}
{"prompt": "\n123 So.2d 102 (1960)\nElsie Roberts RYAN\nv.\nErnest L", "expected": ". RYAN.\n6 Div. 562.\nSupreme Court of Alabama.\nSeptember 15, 1960.", "actual": ". RYAN.\n4 Div. 669.\nSupreme Court of Alabama.\nNovember 18, 1960.\nRehearing Denied February 5, 1961.\n*103 John M. Milling and Joseph R. Milling, Jr., Montgomery, for appellant.\nLange, Simpson, Robinson & Somerville, Birmingham, for appellee.\nSIMPSON, Justice.\nElsie Roberts Ryan, appellant here, instituted this appeal from an order of the Circuit Court of Montgomery County dismissing her suit for divorce on the ground of \"insanity,\" and from the further order overruling"}
{"prompt": "The last M.A.S.H. is decommissioned\n\nSaturday\n\nFeb 16, 2013 at 12", "expected": ":01 AM\n\nThe last M.A.S.H. is decommissioned\n\nLiz Davis\n", "actual": ":01 AMFeb 16, 2013 at 11:12 AM\n\nYou don't see them all that often anymore. At least, not on TV.\n\nThe last of the M.A.S.H. films has been retired.\n\nThe one and only film franchise that helped bring to life a vast array of military and civilian characters from the war zone of Southeast Asia that were not in the book – the United States Marine Corps.\n\nThe Marine Corps Movie and Television (M.A.C.T.) series is a spinoff of the M.A.S.H. movie franchise"}
{"prompt": "Businessmen live in fear and bankers are afraid to lend, the former PM wrote in The Hindu\n\nFormer Prime Minister Man", "expected": "mohan Singh has blasted the BJP’s handling of the economy, blaming the sharp downturn in GDP growth on the �", "actual": "mohan Singh speaks at the launch of his book on the politics of the 21st century at the Press Club, New Delhi on March 06, 2017. PTG | Photo Credit: PTI\n\nFormer Prime Minister Manmohan Singh writes that there must be a change in the way that corporate houses are treated in the country to remove this fear factor.\n\nFacing elections next year, the Congress government is losing the battle to the BJP-led governments at the Centre and state levels led by Prime Minister Narendra Modi and Chief Minister of Gujarat, Narendra Modi.\n\nIn his new book, The Politics of the"}
{"prompt": " \nKJV Foundation Study Bible\n\nNASHVILLE DALLAS MEXICO CITY RIO DE JANEIRO", "expected": "\n\nwww.ThomasNelson.com\n_KJV Foundation Study Bible_\n\nCopyright © 2015 by Thomas Nelson", "actual": "   \nLONDON GIRARDO BERLIN SOUTH KOREA\n\n# **_The KJV Study Bible_**\n\n# **THE STUDY BIBLE **\n\nBible Study in Basic English\n\nCopyright © 1978, 1979, 1980, 1981, 1983, 1984, 1985, 1986, 1987, 1988, 1989, 1990, 1992, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2005, 2007, 2015 by Calvin College\n\nAll rights reserved. No part of this book may be used or reproduced in any manner"}
{"prompt": "Resources\n\nStewardship Plan\n\nA Woodland Stewardship Plan is a must of every owner of 20 or", "expected": " more wooded acres—and it’s very affordable! That is why 80% of MFA members already have a", "actual": " more acres of forest land. It serves to establish a permanent and meaningful relationship between the land and the people who rely on it for sustenance, for recreation, for education, for health, and for economic development. The plan’s purpose is to provide a basis for responsible stewardship of the land, the forest, its products, and the communities, towns, and villages that depend on them for economic and social benefits. A Woodland Stewardship Plan (“Plan”) is a document that identifies the land and its natural and human resources in detail, identifies goals or purposes for the land and its"}
{"prompt": "import SPELLS from 'common/SPELLS';\nimport RushingJadeWind from './RushingJ", "expected": "adeWind';\n\nconst talentlessCombatant = {\n  hasTalent: () => false,\n};\n", "actual": "adeWind';\n\nconst META_KEYWORDS = [\n\t/**\n\t * Invisibility, which allows the target to be hidden from sight and avoids revealing their position. This is useful for hiding the targets.\n\t */\n\t'blink',\n\t'blind',\n\t'darkness',\n\t'detection',\n\t'detection',\n\t'detox',\n\t'disguise',\n\t'deceive',\n\t'display',\n\t'drochus',\n\t'earth',\n\t'earth-drone',\n\t"}
{"prompt": "hi every one. ok i have a 90 535i i went to costa rica a few weeks ago and left", "expected": " my car out side locked. its bout -30 out and i cant get into it. ive tried holding the door handles", "actual": " 2 days after with a man who would have never of took me out there would never have done it i am still mad i could have gotten the money off my own boat and i still would of it was still in the bay area and i could have used it for the down payment on my new boat i just know it was a mistake on my part i should have just rented a cuddy and put the money in my account and not spent it like i was planning to. anyways for the record i am not mad the man that stole it took it to marlin for my boat he said he could not have it out for"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nComo faço para gerar números aleatórios entre 5 e", "expected": " 30 em Java?\n\nPreciso usar o método random e armazená-lo em u", "actual": " 9?\n\nEstou tentando estudar C no segundo semestre e estou com problemas em como programar um programa que não consigo resolver.\n\nEm um sistema de segurança de entrada, gostaria de fazer um programa que receba de 5 a 9 números aleatórios, e depois gerar duas tabelas com os resultados de cada um, usando algumas linguagens estudadas, incluindo C?\n\nJá"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nCollapse nD numpy array into a 1D array\n\nI am trying to sum the values", "expected": " of a nD array along a particular axis to effectively collapse it into a 1D array.\nI have been looking through", "actual": " of a numpy array across the rows and then collapse the resulting array into a 1D array. I am using the following code:\nimport numpy as np\n\nN = 1000\n\nnDArray = np.zeros((N, 1000))\n\nfor i in range(0, N):\n    nDArray[i, 1] += 10\n\nAnd this gives me this:\narray([[ 0.  ],\n       [ 10.],\n       [ 20.],\n       [ 30"}
{"prompt": "Braidon Burns\n\nBraidon Burns (born 8 July 1996) is an Australian professional rugby league footballer who plays", "expected": " as a  and er for the South Sydney Rabbitohs in the NRL.\n\nBackground\nBurns was born in", "actual": " as a  for the Manly Warringah Sea Eagles in the NRL and New Zealand City in the Intrust Super Premiership (ISP).\n\nBurns has played for the Manly-Warringah Sea Eagles, St. George Illawarra Dragons and the Auckland Warriors and played for the New Zealand national rugby league team at the 2017 World Cup.\n\nBackground\nBurns was born in Perth, Western Australia.\n\nHe is of Indigenous Australian heritage, and is of part Choctaw descent.  Burns was educated at St. Ignatius College, Riverton.\n\nEarly career\n"}
{"prompt": "Fluctuation-induced heat release from temperature-quenched nuclear spins near a quantum critical point.\nAt a", "expected": " quantum critical point (QCP)--a zero-temperature singularity in which a line of continuous phase transition terminates--", "actual": " quantum critical point (QCP), a macroscopic system goes through a continuous phase transition driven by a large change in the microscopic properties of its constituents. In this paper, we present a thermodynamic calculation of nuclear heat release caused by the thermal fluctuations near a quantum critical point (QCP) of the three-dimensional classical Ising spin chain with magnetic field. We consider a regime where the field is much smaller than the other relevant physical parameters and the temperature is low enough for the quantum system to be effectively temperature-quenched. By using Monte Carlo simulations, we measure the heat release at the QCP in the"}
{"prompt": "<?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"utf-8\"?>\n<RelativeLayout xmlns:android=\"", "expected": "http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android\"\n    style=\"@style", "actual": "http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android\"\n    android:layout_width=\"fill_parent\"\n    android:layout_height=\"fill_parent\"\n    >\n<include\n    android:id=\"@+id/root_view\"\n    layout=\"@layout/main_fragment\"\n    layout_width=\"match_parent\"\n    layout_height=\"match_parent\"\n    />\n</RelativeLayout>\n\nfragment_"}
{"prompt": "10. Eliud Kipchoge, marathon runner\n\npicture alliance / picture alliance / Getty\n\nFew athletes had", "expected": " as dominant a 2018 as Kenyan distance runner Eliud Kipchoge. The 33-year-old has won 10 of", "actual": " a bigger impact on the field than Eliud Kipchoge, who not only finished first in the men's marathon in the London 2012 Olympic Games but also set an Olympic record in the race. Kipchoge finished the marathon in 2:09:54, more than half an hour faster than the previous record, which he had set in Berlin in 2008. He also set a new marathon record for the Boston Marathon, which he finished in the second-fastest time ever clocked by a South African runner, 2:08:07.\n\n11. John Woodcock, footballer\n\nJohn Woodcock"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nRefer a manage bean from other project\n\nI use Google App Engine 1.9.51. ", "expected": " In Eclipse I create 4 projects for multi-services: \n- One Ear (GoalsCompletion)\n- One", "actual": "\nI'm doing the following thing... \nIn one JAVA project (lets call it PROJ), I want to manage a bean (let's call it User) which has following dependencies:\n\njdbc:mysql://my_db_name;bind=key_value\njpa:hibernate=sql\n\nIn another, let's call it PROJ_SERVEN. \nThis PROJ have an interface named UserService which is using the User managed in PROJ, using User.getAll(), and then creating a User with that list.\nIn PRO"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nLinq to XML data structure\n\nThis is my XML:\n<home>\n  <cont", "expected": "ents>\n    <row>\n        <content>\n    ", "actual": "ribution>\n    <contributor>\n      <name>Peter</name>\n      <role>Writer</role>\n    </contributor>\n    <contributor>\n      <name>Bob</name>\n      <role>Follower</role>\n    </contributor>\n  </contribution>\n\n  <contribution>\n    <contributor>\n      <name>Peter</name>"}
{"prompt": "A typical such apparatus uses a roller in which is seated at least one rocker-type measuring bar or beam generally flush with", "expected": " the cylindrical outer surface of the roller and supported on sensors, for example force measurers, preferably piezo elements.", "actual": " the bottom surface of its support, and which is engaged in a bearing between a guide tube, whose bottom surface is essentially horizontal, and the guide tube is supported on the topmost face of an associated table. The measurement of the deflection of the bar during the passage of an object therein can be carried out by a displacement transducer, which is fixed in the guide tube and which is disposed at the bottom end of the roller.\nOne of the reasons for using such a roller is the following: the roller requires a very large bearing area to be able to accommodate and bear the weight of the instrument and must be"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nwhy return change variables while inside a class\n\nI cannot understand this ruby behavior, the code explains better", "expected": " what I mean:   \nclass DoNotUnderstand\n    def initialize\n     ", "actual": " with a class definition. The idea is that when a user inputs a variable that is not set inside a class then we do something different to the normal behavior in Ruby.\nclass TestApp\n\n  attr_accessor :app\n\n  def initialize(app)   \n    @app = app\n  end\n\n  def load\n    return unless app.is_a?(TestApp)\n  end\n\n  def get_var\n    return if app.get_var_from_input\n  end\n\n  def get_value\n   "}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThe present invention relates generally to protective head gear for a firefighter, and more particularly, but", "expected": " not by way of limitation, to an improved firefighting hood and face mask assembly.\n2. Brief Description of the Related", "actual": " not by way of limitation, to a protective headgear having enhanced ability to block the inhalation of water vapors as the firefighter enters air-supplied chambers, such as a firefighting apparatus.\n2. Description of the Related Art\nA significant and ever increasing number of fires have been created over recent years due to the increased use of flammable materials in many construction materials. Firefighting systems, such as trucks and firefighting apparatus, which are the subject of the present invention, are commonly utilized to fight such fires in homes, office buildings and other structures. The success of the firefighting system depends on the"}
{"prompt": "Test non-inferiority (and equivalence) based on the odds ratio under a simple crossover trial.\nFor", "expected": " testing the non-inferiority (or equivalence) of a generic drug to a standard drug, the odds ratio", "actual": " the first time, this paper aims to demonstrate how a single non-inferiority test can be carried out based on the odds ratio under a simple crossover trial. Under this 'simple crossover trial', the test statistic can be obtained after one trial based on the odds ratio by simple addition and the variance under the crossover trial can be obtained as the ratio of the test statistic and the variance of the crossover trial. Under the generalized crossover trial and the simple crossover trial, the non-inferiority tests are obtained by the likelihood ratio tests when the standard hypothesis is the fixed one between treatment and control and it is rejected"}
{"prompt": "the mechanical man of my dreams", "expected": "", "actual": "' is what you're waiting for? Or is he that much of a monster you refuse to recognize?\"\n\n\"Oh, come now. I'm the one who's in awe.\"\n\n\"You're afraid of him.\"\n\n\"Of course I'm afraid of him, too. In point of fact, I was just a teeny weeny bit amused by the thought of a man who goes through life not knowing where he came from. Don't you see? It would take years for him to learn I exist!\"\n\n\"A person can only learn so much about someone they're already familiar with.\"\n\n\"Yes, but he's not someone!\"\n\n\"But you said yourself"}
{"prompt": "Human monoclonal anti-Plasmodium falciparum antibodies produced by stable EBV-transformed", "expected": " lymphocytes from patients with falciparum malaria.\nPeripheral blood lymphocytes (PBL) from 10", "actual": " human cells persist for up to 200 days in murine plasma.\nProduction of IgG anti-P. falciparum has been proposed to be a useful therapeutic approach for falciparum malaria. A recombinant EBV-transformed cell line (W2) that secretes antibodies and cytophilic antigens of P. falciparum was used to derive a murine anti-P. falciparum hybridoma. The cell line had the ability to secrete a stable IgG-antibody fraction, but no stable IgM or IgA-ant"}
{"prompt": "UPDATE: Forks man held on $30K bail after firing gun to'menace' wife, police say\n\n\n", "expected": "\nA man fired a gunshot during a domestic disturbance Sunday afternoon in a Forks Township home, police reported.\n\nOfficers", "actual": "\nThe man allegedly used his fork to smash a window and then forced his way into a neighbor's home and threatened to kill himself.\n\nPolice say the man, 35, lived in the North Ridge home where one of the victims, 40-year-old Shari Paine, and her husband lived.\n\nThe woman was reportedly a \"full-time student and part-time caregiver\" at the home.\n\nAuthorities say the man fired a shotgun blast at Paine's home, prompting Paine to take the family dog and leave with the family car.\n\nAccording to the incident report,"}
{"prompt": "<?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"UTF-8\"?>\n<!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC", "expected": " \"-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN\" \"http://www.apple.com/DTD", "actual": " \"-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN\" \"http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd\">\n<plist version=\"1.0\">\n<dict>\n\t<key>Ansi 0 Color</key>\n\t<dict>\n\t\t<key>Blue Component</key>\n\t\t<real>0.10588235294117647</real>\n\t\t<key>Green Component</key>\n\t\t<real>0.06422715060166797</real"}
{"prompt": "Routine measurement of fluoxetine and norfluoxetine by high-performance liquid chromatography with ultraviolet detection in", "expected": " patients under concomitant treatment with tricyclic antidepressants.\nA robust and rapid high-performance liquid chromatography (", "actual": " the neonate.\nThe determination of norfluoxetine and fluoxetine concentrations in serum and breast milk from mothers of term and preterm infants was performed using a high-performance liquid chromatographic method with the fluorescence detector. After protein precipitation with methanol, serum samples were chromatographed on a C18 column with a mobile phase containing acetonitrile and aqueous 0.02 M potassium dihydrogen phosphate buffer, pH 2.2. Breast milk samples were chromatographed on a C8 column with the mobile phase containing acetonitrile and 0.03 M potassium"}
{"prompt": "Roald Dahl James And The Giant Peach Hydration Bottle\n\nCode: 5233211\n\nDescription\n\nAn", "expected": " adventurous piece for children’s drinks on the go, this hydration bottle is from the James and the Giant Peach collection", "actual": " adorable new addition to the world of science fiction—James and the Giant Peach is a book of short stories about a boy and his mysterious vegetable—the Giant Peach—a.k.a. Peter, who is now grown up and is an engineer. With Peter's help, James has created and tested his own hydration system—a huge black-and-white plastic water bottle that can carry and store a great quantity of water, even in temperatures as low as 45 degrees Fahrenheit.\n\nDescription\n\nAn adorable new addition to the world of science fiction—James and the Giant Peach is a book of short stories"}
{"prompt": "The Cure for Toothache Pain\n\nFebruary 15, 2013\n\nThe first couple of months of every year I seem to", "expected": " spend dealing with one sickness after the other. Going through my archives is kind of hilarious as year after year I spend January dealing", "actual": " be in a perpetual state of toothache. I seem to get more of them in the summer, and less in the winter, and they usually come around around my birthday (which is two days after my birthday). My teeth, and my mouth, are like an old broken machine. One day it works just fine, and the next it won’t. I’m talking about a toothache that’s intense. A toothache that goes on almost like clockwork (literally). And it can be pretty damn uncomfortable too.\n\nMy first toothache was when I was 8. I have 4"}
{"prompt": "Mechanisms of genomic imprinting.\nA small number of mammalian genes undergo the process of genomic imprinting whereby the expression", "expected": " level of the alleles of a gene depends upon their parental origin. In the past year, attention has focused on the mechanisms", "actual": " of one allele is exclusively dependent upon whether the allele is inherited from one parent or another. To date, only a handful of imprinted genes have been shown to function as either maternal or paternal imprinted genes. A number of biological functions have been attributed to imprinted genes, such as embryogenesis and spermatogenesis, and genomic imprinting has been shown to impact on the expression of a wide variety of genes, including many imprinted tumor suppressor genes and oncogenes. The mammalian genome is thought to have been imprinted early in its evolutionary history as a result of a series of somatic cell divisions,"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nHow to count the number of anchor tags within a div using javascript?\n\nI want to know how", "expected": " to count the number of anchor tags present within a div element.\ne.g.:\n<div>\n<a", "actual": " can i count the number of anchor tags within a div using javascript? I tried using this function but its not working fine.\nIt counts the anchor tags only inside the tag and not outside the tag.\n<div id='demo_div'><div id='demo_div_title'><p>Title 1</p><p>Title 2</p><p>Title 3</p> <p>Title 4</p><p>Title 5</p><p>Title 6</p><p>Title 7</p><p>Title 8</p></div><div class='"}
{"prompt": "Docker Community Forums\n\nI have a program running inside a docker container and I expose the port 8888. However,", "expected": " when I try to connect the program from a device (in the same LAN as host machine but not the host machine) it", "actual": " when I try to connect to the endpoint, I don't know how to do it, it says the port is wrong, so I go to docker.io and try to expose the port there.\nBut how is port 8888 different from anything else like 8080 or 9090 or so?\nEDIT:\nIn addition, I tried to connect to docker.io through terminal. But the result I can see is:\ndocker: Error response from daemon: PORT is not allowed to use the \"default-gateway\"\ndocker: Error response from daemon: Unauthorized\ndocker: Error response from daemon"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nCan we add properties to immutable object in JavaScript?\n\nAn object is like: \nconst obj", "expected": " = [{name: 'Alex', age: 20}, {name: 'James', age: 22}];\n\n", "actual": " = {\n  foo: 'bar',\n}\n\nCan we write a JavaScript function addProperties which will add properties to objects?\nconst obj = {\n  foo: 'bar',\n}\nobj.addProperties(\n  {\n    bar: 'baz',\n  },\n  {\n    baz: 'qux',\n  }\n);\n\nIn other words :\nlet {a,b} = obj;\nobj.a + 'b';     // result {'a':'bar', 'b':"}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThe present invention generally relates to an optical device for optically connecting a pair of optical fibers", "expected": " (a first and a second optical fiber) and, more particularly, relates to an optical device having two or more functions including", "actual": ", and more particularly, to an optical device for aligning and connecting a pair of optical fibers in a non-contact manner.\n2. Description of the Related Art\nAlong with the recent trend towards higher performance of information communication devices, there is demand for further enhancement of the speed and reliability of such devices. The demand also places high demands on the performance of optical devices for optically connecting a pair of optical fibers (for example, a pair of optical fibers used in wavelength division multiplexing (WDM) optical communication) of an information communication device. For example, such a device must be capable of optically"}
{"prompt": "Given the prevalence of anti-camping laws in the U.S., many more people could follow suit. According to a", "expected": " National Law Center on Homelessness & Poverty report analyzing 187 U.S. cities, more than half prohibit camping, sitting,", "actual": " 2011 analysis by the advocacy group American Civil Liberties Union, 40 states have laws or laws pending in their legislatures that would make it illegal for someone to go to a public place that is closed to the public -- often a beach or state park -- with some type of personal camping device, such as a tent or trailer. The group also found that there were more than 200 bills in the 113th Congress that would allow people to be arrested and prosecuted for \"camping within sight\" at more than 1,600 locations.\n\nThe ACLU has sued to repeal or strengthen more than a dozen of the laws. In New Jersey,"}
{"prompt": "Introduction {#s1}\n============\n\nAs humans live in societies, they are more or less social and interw", "expected": "oven in the society [@pone.0091975-Aronson1]. Given that humans significantly rely on social relationships to", "actual": "oven with them. With the exception of humans in their ancestral environment, all multicellular life forms have developed a sophisticated social system in which they cooperate and communicate with each other. The emergence of social structures and interactions can be viewed as a complex biological process, which was probably initially achieved by evolution through genetic conflicts or mutations [@pone.0026293-Pigliucci1]--[@pone.0026293-Lang1]. Nevertheless, the evolutionary success of social systems and their biological function are still debated. In this paper, we investigate the roles of the evolutionary history of life-forms"}
{"prompt": "OWINGS MILLS, Md. -- Left tackle Eugene Monroe is scheduled to undergo a magnetic resonance imaging test on his shoulder Wednesday", "expected": ", which could add some clarity to one of the more uncertain positions on the Baltimore Ravens this season.\n\n\"Between him", "actual": ".\n\nMonroe told reporters after practice that he won't travel with the team to Indianapolis during the bye week, but he has not ruled out his availability for next week's game against the Bengals. Left guard Joe Thomas will start at right guard for the Bills."}
{"prompt": "<?php\n// +----------------------------------------------------------------------\n// | ThinkPHP [ WE CAN DO IT JUST THINK ]\n// +", "expected": "----------------------------------------------------------------------\n// | Copyright (c) 2006~2017 http://thinkphp.cn All rights reserved.\n// +", "actual": "----------------------------------------------------------------------\n// | Copyright (c) 2006~2018 http://thinkphp.cn All rights reserved.\n// +----------------------------------------------------------------------\n// | Licensed ( http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 )\n// +----------------------------------------------------------------------\n// | Author: liu21st <liu21st@gmail.com>\n// +----------------------------------------------------------------------\n\nnamespace think;\n\nuse think\\db\\Query;\nuse think\\exception\\ValidateDataTypeException;\n\nclass QueryLanguage\n{\n    //运行的"}
{"prompt": "1. Introduction {#sec1}\n===============\n\nCRMO (chronic recurrent multifocal osteomyelitis", "expected": ") also known as chronic nonbacterial osteomyelitis is an inflammatory disease of the bone that frequently occurs in children \\", "actual": ") is a rare heterogenous group of chronic inflammatory diseases of bone and/or skin, affecting up to 1 to 2 persons per million of the general population. It is characterized by multiple lytic, subperiosteal, sub-epicondylar, and intercondylar bone lesions with radiographic appearance of multifocal lytic lesions, often with an ill-defined margins, representing different stages of bone destruction \\[[@B1]\\]. The disease is almost always associated with inflammatory joint symptoms that are the clinical basis for a diagnosis \\[[@B1]\\]. The diagnosis should include clinical"}
{"prompt": "Artur Sagitov\n\nArtur Damirovich Sagitov (; born 7 January 2000) is a Russian", "expected": " football player. He plays as a centre-forward for FC Nizhny Novgorod on loan from FC Rubin Kaz", "actual": " ice hockey player. He is currently plays with Moscow Dynamo of the Kontinental Hockey League (KHL). Sagitov made his KHL debut playing with Metallurg Aeros and has skated in the KHL for the Aeros, HC Lada Togliatti, Torpedo Nizhny Novgorod, and Metallurg Magnitogorsk. Sagitov was selected to play for Russia at the 2018 World Juniors.\n\nPlaying career\n\nHigh school and college\nSagitov played for the youth team of Metallurg Magnitogorsk before they won"}
{"prompt": "622 F.2d 576\nU. S.v.Amen\n79-1347\nUNITED", "expected": " STATES COURT OF APPEALS Second Circuit\n3/10/80\n\n1\nE.D.N.Y", "actual": " STATES COURT OF APPEALS Second Circuit\n6/30/80\n\n1\nE.D.N.Y., 444 F.Supp. 532\n\nU.S.C.P.\n\n\n2\nPETITION FOR REHEARING EN BANC DENIED*\n\n\n\n*\nEN BANC ORDERED PER CURIAM**\n\n\n\n3\nS.D.N.Y.\n\n\n4\nA-527-80\n\n\n5\nU.S. v. Amen\n\n\n\n*\n Petition for rehearing en banc was considered by the"}
{"prompt": "StartChar: uni0620.medi_BaaNonFina\nEncoding: 1116379 -1 25", "expected": "51\nWidth: 218\nFlags: HW\nAnchorPoint: \"TashkilAbove\" -0 801", "actual": "73\nWidth: 612\nFlags: HW\nAnchorPoint: \"TashkilAbove\" 5 801 basechar 0\nAnchorPoint: \"TashkilBelow\" 292 -265 basechar 0\nLayerCount: 3\nFore\nRefer: 207 -1 N 1 0 0 1 0 0 2\nRefer: 153 -1 N 1 0 0 1 0 0 3\nEndChar\nStartChar: uni0625.medi_Bb\nEncoding: 1116379 -1 2479\nWidth: 621\nFlags: HW\nAnchorPoint: \"End"}
{"prompt": "An article at The Atlantic by Miles Kimball and Noah Smith argues against the notion that some people are just not “math", "expected": " people” and I couldn’t agree more:\n\n… we believe that the idea of “math people", "actual": "-y” and that we should use the power of math to understand how to best navigate a world of data. While much (and I mean much, and I would assume most) of the article argues against the notion that math is relevant in every area of life, one of the most important themes that they present is a challenge of how to use data to understand what is going on and what to do next.\n\nThe challenge is that we have gotten very good at finding patterns, and what is going on behind the patterns, but we don’t understand how to connect the dots, and to whom to"}
{"prompt": "Two-step (dance move)\n\nThe two-step is a step found in various dances, including many folk", "expected": " dances. \n\nA two-step consists of two steps in approximately the same direction onto the same foot, separated by", "actual": " dances in Europe, and in several Latin American dances, and in the Mexican moleca.\n\nHistory\nThe two-step originated in Europe, where it is sometimes considered a precursor to the cha-cha-cha and the quickstep. In the nineteenth century, it was used in the waltz in the first popular dance in America, the foxtrot.\n\nOne of the first two-steppers in the Western world was the Cuban fandango, which was the precursor dance to the American foxtrot. The fandango has remained in Cuba to the present day, where it is performed"}
{"prompt": "Melzerella monnei\n\nMelzerella monnei is a species of beetle in the family Ceramby", "expected": "cidae. It was described by Wappes and Lingafelter in 2011.\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:", "actual": "cidae (\"brown-winged beetles\"), of which it is the type species. The species was originally described by Linnaeus in 1758, and is named after Charles Monard. M. monnei is native to Europe, Asia, Africa, and North America.\n\nM. monnei is a parasite of numerous hosts including the larval and gall midge (Hirudo medicinalis) in Europe, and the gall midge (Tephritis pumilio) and honeybee (Apis mellifera) in East Asia. It is also found on the gall midge in"}
{"prompt": "Clinical and manometric findings on elderly patients with achalasia.\nData regarding the age impact on the clinical presentation and", "expected": " esophageal motility in adults with idiopathic achalasia are scarce. To asses the clinical and man", "actual": " treatment of achalasia are lacking. The aim of this study was to evaluate the incidence and severity of achalasia in older patients compared with younger ones. All patients (≥ 60 years) with achalasia referred to our department during a 5-year period (from January 2009 to December 2013) were included in a retrospective study. Seventy-eight patients (38 males, median age 67 years [range 60 to 82 years]) were included. The median follow-up period was 2.1 years. Based on the modified Eckardt score, the incidences of achalasia type I, type II"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nJavaScript ternary operator and if/else statement\n\nCan anyone explain to me what is the", "expected": " difference between these two statements and why the second one does not work and the first one does:\n\nif (finalWord", "actual": " reason of the error in the code below?\nIt is an if/else statement with a ternary operator. I can't tell what the error is.\nIs it a typo and there is a syntax error in the ternary operator?\nThanks.\nERROR: Uncaught TypeError: undefined is not a function at HTMLDivElement.js:21\nP.S. The second condition is false.\nvar currentUser = null;\nvar userId = null;\n\n    if() {\n        if(currentUser === true) {\n\n "}
{"prompt": "Role of inflammatory pathways in the development and cardiovascular complications of type 2 diabetes.\nExperimental and epidemiologic studies support the", "expected": " role of inflammation in the development of type 2 diabetes and atherosclerosis. Serum levels of inflammatory markers, in particular highly", "actual": " roles of chronic inflammation in the development and cardiovascular complications of type 2 diabetes. Inflammation is a complex process associated with microvascular and macrovascular complications of diabetes. Activation of the innate immune system and monocyte and macrophage infiltration into the walls of small and large vessels may be the mechanism by which chronic inflammation contributes to the development of diabetic complications. Although the contribution of inflammatory markers in the pathogenesis of these complications is unknown, evidence indicates that several factors are likely to play important roles and influence the course of the disease. The interplay between genetic and environmental factors may influence the relative impact of these factors"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nHow to call the objective function of CPLEX from external software?\n\nI would like to know", "expected": " if I can have the objective function of CPLEX called from external software such as R. I built the optimisation model", "actual": " how to call the objective function of CPLEX from external software? For example, if you were to run CPLEX from Matlab or Octave, then you would obtain this output:\n                                             Max residual\n                                      "}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nWhat are some AOE/multi-unit damage items in dota 2?\n\nWe recently had", "expected": " a game were a PL settled on that hero at the last moment, and our team has no heroes with AOE abilities.", "actual": " a game in which a team of 9 players were trying to steal a small gold piece, and we were in the red and blue team. We were losing every game until we decided to combine forces and run a 7v7 brawl against the enemy team. We had an AOE attack that would deal 10-20 damage with 3-3 sec cd's to the enemy team. We managed to kill most of them, and then their only remaining member got killed by us. He also got silenced, so it was a complete wipe. I decided at that moment that we should bring this item from the items bag of the enemy"}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThe invention relates to the field of umbrella/parasol devices and more particularly to an", "expected": " umbrella/parasol with an adjustable tilt feature.\n2. Description of the Related Art\nUmbrellas or", "actual": " arrangement of a plurality of umbrella/parasol devices in a bundle. The present invention includes a plurality of umbrella devices with a plurality of parabola-shaped parabola surfaces, each of which is arranged for folding down and down toward a lower side and includes a plurality of parabola-shaped parabola surfaces. A parabolic arc of movement for a device can be produced by one or more parabola surfaces which, in combination, can be arranged for folding down and up.\nIn this context \"up\" means the direction of movement which leads from the folded position to the erected position, when"}
{"prompt": "### Title: Be as meaningful as possible in 60 chars if possible\n\ninput.scss\n```scss\n", "expected": "test {\n  content: bar\n}\n```\n\n[libsass 3.5.5] [", "actual": "@input-help-label {\n  color: #999;\n  font-weight: bold;\n  position: absolute;\n  top: 0;\n  left: 0;\n}\n\n```\n\n```scss\n/* Make input-help-label to be as meaningful as possible */\n.input-help-label {\n  color: #999;\n  font-weight: bold;\n  position: absolute;\n  top: 0;\n  left: 0;\n}\n```\n\n```scss\n/* Make input-help"}
{"prompt": "﻿<!DOCTYPE html>\r\n<html>\r\n<head>\r\n  ", "expected": "  <meta charset=\"utf-8\" />\r\n    <meta name=\"viewport\" content=\"", "actual": "  <meta charset=\"utf-8\" />\r\n    <meta name=\"viewport\" content=\"width=device-width, initial-scale=1\">\r\n    <title>@ViewData[\"Title\"] - MyLists</title>\r\n    <link rel=\"stylesheet\" href=\"~/lib/bootstrap/dist/css/bootstrap.css\" />\r\n    <link rel=\"stylesheet\" href=\"~/css/site.css\" />\r\n    @RenderSection(\"scripts\", required:"}
{"prompt": "Abstract\n\nBackground\n\nMetformin is widely used in the treatment of diabetes, and there is interest in ‘", "expected": "repurposing’\nthe drug for cancer prevention or treatment. However, the mechanism underlying the\nmetabolic effects of", "actual": "metformin-resistant’ forms of the disease. The aim of this study was to investigate the effects of metformin monotherapy on bone-mineral density, in the osteoporosis prevention arm of the Scottish Diabetes Outcome (Diabetes Prevention Programme) trial.\n\nMethods\n\nWe studied 2,744 postmenopausal women from the DiabCare (Metformin for Osteoporosis Prevention) study who were randomized to 5–15 years of treatment with metformin or placebo in a 16-week single-blind randomized trial lasting to and including 3 years. Bone density"}
{"prompt": "Consumption is a major concept in economics\nand is also studied by many other social sciences.\nEconomists are particularly interested", "expected": " in\nthe relationship between consumption and income,\nand therefore in economics the consumption\nfunction plays a major role.\nDifferent", "actual": " in income\nand wealth. According to many economists, the\namount of resources that people have at their\ndisposal is what decides the well-being of\nsociety,\nincluding how happy people are and their quality\nof life.\nEconomists have identified numerous factors\nthat influence well-being\nand have devised a variety of models to explain\nhow they affect people’s lives.\nThese have been refined over the years to\nbe able to explain many aspects of well-being.\nEconomists also study the distribution of income\nand wealth, which affect the well-being of\nsoc"}
{"prompt": "Chrysoroyiatissa Monastery\n\nChrysoroyiatissa (Greek: Χρυσ", "expected": "ορρογιάτισσα) is a monastery dedicated to Our Lady of the Golden P", "actual": "ούηδιττός, lit.: Ἁρόςορόςιος; English: The Beautiful and the Good) Monastery is a Greek Orthodox monastery in the outskirts of Kavala and Pjestari city of Macedonia, Greece. It was founded in the late 1930s by Greek Orthodox Patriarch Ieronymos in his home town of Kavala. The monastery was founded as a school for boys (St. John of the Cross, Kavala).\n\nThe monastery is the largest and oldest in Pjestari"}
{"prompt": "Carly Rae Jepsen Covers Cosmopolitan January 2013\n\nThe 27-year-old singer looked picture perfect in", "expected": " tousled hair and a funky skater-girl dress for the front page while opening up about topics including Justin Bieber to", "actual": " a pink and black Chanel suit - but her hair was a mess. Luckily, one stylist on the show helped her tame it.\n\nAs she talked about her relationship to music, it was revealed that she has a \"little bit of an attitude\".\n\nOn whether it was hard being the youngest person in the room, she said: \"It was, no, I think it was really, really, super, super fun to have a little bit of an attitude.\n\n\"It was really nice to go to concerts, because they're really small and you get to see bands from a smaller generation"}
{"prompt": "Sterl, M. F., Delandmeter, P., & van Sebille, E. (2020). Influence", "expected": " of barotropic tidal currents on transport and accumulation of floating microplastics in the global open ocean. Journal of Geophysical Research", "actual": " of wind on the development of land-use intensity and the carbon sink in the Netherlands. Ecology and Society, 6, e20150213. 10.1002/ers1321\n\n1. Introduction {#ers1321-sec-0001}\n===============\n\nWind energy is a key renewable energy source in the Netherlands. It is currently the largest source for renewable energy in a sustainable climate. Despite this fact, the potential contribution of wind energy, as well as other renewable energy sources, to the national energy supply still warrants continued research, and there is no simple rule of thumb about how much wind energy"}
{"prompt": "Touch modulates gravity sensing to regulate the growth of primary roots of Arabidopsis thaliana.\nPlants must sense", "expected": " and respond to diverse stimuli to optimize the architecture of their root system for water and nutrient scavenging and anchorage. We have", "actual": " and adjust their roots to changes in environmental conditions such as root competition, biotic and abiotic stresses. Gravity sensing appears to be involved in the growth regulation of plants because gravisensing mutants exhibit growth defects. However, the relationship between gravity sensing and growth regulation is still unclear. Here we report that the gravity-sensing CIM (coordinated in movement) protein modulates the growth of primary roots by regulating the gravitropic response. In particular, we found that CIM acts as a negative regulator of the gravitropic response by specifically downregulating the growth of primary roots to a degree inversely"}
{"prompt": "NOTE:\nThis guide is applicable only for Samsung’s Galaxy S2 (S II) international version (i9", "expected": "100). Check your phone’s version in Settings – About Phone. It has to be “GT-i9", "actual": "100). The following steps will not work for anyone who bought their Galaxy S II in India (HTC EVO) (iM8500).\n\nNote:\nThis is not an official Samsung Galaxy S2 (S II) (i9100) (HTC EVO) (iM8500) manual; it is just a guide for Samsung Galaxy S II (S II) (HTC EVO) (iM8500) for the purpose of helping the user to follow these steps. The steps are also same as the original ones provided by Samsung for its Galaxy S II (S II"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nCalculating number of days per quarter for two dates\n\nSo, I have a project where if", "expected": " given two dates I need to calculate the number of days between them that is in each quarter. In theory I could use NETWORK", "actual": " a client enters in a starting date (say, January 1st) and an ending date (say, March 30th) I need to find out how many days (3 days) of the quarter were not performed. So, this is what I want:\nJanuary 1st, 2018:\n3 days\nJanuary 2nd, 2018:\n3 days\nJanuary 3rd, 2018:\n3 days\n...\nJanuary 30, 2018:\n3 days\nJanuary 1st, 2019:\n3 days\nJanuary 2nd, 2019:\n3 days\nJanuary 3rd, 2019:\n3 days\n\n"}
{"prompt": "Binding of Ca2+ to phosphoinositols, phosphatidylserines and gangliosides.\n", "expected": "The effect of K+, Mg2+ and serotonin on the interaction between Ca2+ and different phospholipids as", "actual": "The Ca2+ -dependent phosphoinositide binding activity in serum and membrane preparations was studied. It was found that both preparations required Ca2+ for full activity, and that the Ca2+ -dependent activity was different from the inositol phosphate-dependent activity. Serum or synovial fluid contained low levels of phosphatidylinositol (PI) and phosphatidylserine (PS). PI and phosphatidylcholine were major phospholipids in both serum and synovial fluid. Phosphatidylcholine, PS and PI could not be labeled with"}
{"prompt": "A tennis player has abandoned her Australian Open qualifier mid-match after an intense coughing fit amid heavy bushfire smoke in Melbourne.", "expected": "\n\nKey points: Slovenian Dalila Jakupovic suffered a severe coughing fit on court and was forced to retire from", "actual": "\n\nAlexandra Dulgheru, 18, was left coughing for nearly an hour in the first set against Samantha Stosur, who has since retired from the tournament.\n\nThe pair faced off in a quarterfinal on Thursday, and Dulgheru was clearly struggling with the heavy smoke.\n\nIn a desperate attempt the Australian Open teenager grabbed Stosur's racquet before the match was even completed.\n\nDulgheru was left wracked with coughing, but the world No. 39 overcame the problem to progress to the next round.\n\nThe girl later admitted she \"did"}
{"prompt": "3 + f*t**4 and give p.\n-8\nRearrange 5*b + 691 +", "expected": " 3*b - 3*b - 690 to the form r*b + i and give i.\n1\n", "actual": " 8*b - 3*b - 393 + (-2 + 2 + 2)*(-3*b + 3*b - b) to y + n*b and give n.\n2\nRearrange -11*z + 2*z**2 + 2 + 4*z**2 + 12*z + 12*z**2 - 2*z**2 to i*z**2 + p*z + m and give p.\n-1\nExpress (-3*r**2 + 5*r**2 - 3*r**2 + (-r - r + 4"}
{"prompt": "Back in 2017, I was at work (at a gaming cafe) when one of the guests who came to visit us introduced", "expected": " themselves as an employee of Wizards Of The Coast, the publisher behind Magic: The Gathering. While I’d heard about", "actual": " us to a young lad who was spending his summer working in the basement of his family home. We were to have a couple of beers together and talk about his work at the cafe and the future of gaming as we know it. Before we knew it, we were being invited to the guest’s home to have more beers and talk about his future as a young lad in the industry.\n\nI knew the lad as I had been there with him when he played his copy of the game, Super Mario 64. He was a tall lad but I am sure he would have been no taller than 5’6"}
{"prompt": "Build Muscle or Lose Fat Survey\n\nMark aka The Old Spartan and Over-50 Fitness Savior is a 63 year old coffee", "expected": " guzzling father of five wandering the outdoors around Albuquerque, New Mexico. Mark helps Active Boomers get lean, healthy and", "actual": " drinker, former Navy SEAL, martial arts instructor, personal trainer, and exercise physiologist. He has battled every disease known to man (other than the plague), and lived to see the future. He wrote a blog years ago (before that blog had a website) about the importance of nutrition on health. His blog is still up and he is still trying to get his message across. He has over 3000 blog followers. He started the Old Spartan because he felt like he was fighting a losing battle. Over the years, Mark had gained weight, and he wanted to take action to control his health. This blog is his"}
{"prompt": "by David P. Greisman\n\nMarlon Sullivan, manager of junior welterweight contender Karim Mayfield,", "expected": " is not in Atlantic City to see Mayfield face Thomas Dulorme this weekend. That’s because Sullivan was arrested", "actual": " says he has plans to take a fight in the near future between himself and Junior dos Santos.\n\nDos Santos has been out of action since April when he stopped WBA world titleholder Carlos Condit in a controversial decision for his WBA 'Super' Welterweight Title on April 25. Dos Santos, who has been stripped of the title, is still awaiting his mandatory title defence against current WBA and WBO super middleweight champion David Avanesyan in September.\n\nDos Santos' trainer, Freddie Roach, has said he feels confident that he will be called back to the ring in May"}
{"prompt": "/* Copyright 1988,1990,1993,1994 by Paul Vixie\n * All rights reserved\n */\n\n/*\n *", "expected": " Copyright (c) 2004 by Internet Systems Consortium, Inc. (\"ISC\")\n * Copyright (c) 1997,2000 by", "actual": " OpenEXR - R10G (R10 G,R10 B,C) bitmap file loader\n */\n\n#include <stdio.h>\n#include <stdlib.h>\n#include <string.h>\n#include <ctype.h>\n#include <math.h>\n#include <GL/gl.h>\n#include \"exr.h\"\n#include \"file.h\"\n#include \"m_debug.h\"\n#include \"pars.h\"\n#include \"utils.h\"\n#include"}
{"prompt": "The shrill whistle by Brendan Rodgers that typically calls an end to Liverpool training sessions is rarely the signal for Danny Ings to", "expected": " bring his own work to a conclusion.\n\nInstead, the striker will seek out a member of the coaching staff to remain", "actual": " launch an attack. The forward was one of a handful of players to depart Anfield before the start of the Reds’ season opener against Bournemouth, and he’ll be a free agent soon, with only a £25m sell-on clause as his only inducement to play for the club again.\n\nIngs’ position is more that of a cautionary tale – the latest casualty of a Liverpool squad that has underperformed of late and now looks as though it may miss out on a Europa League spot to the eventual champions, Tottenham Hotspur, in the event of a late finish to"}
{"prompt": "Attorney General Eric Holder was critical on Monday of “the selective release of sensitive information” from the local investigation of the", "expected": " Ferguson, Mo. police shooting of Michael Brown.\n\n“The selective release of sensitive information that we have seen in", "actual": " New Black Panther Party and other civil rights groups who were investigated by the Justice Department for their “lawless” actions.\n\nThe DOJ announced on Monday that it was releasing information from the case of New Black Panther Party v. Eric Holder, in which the Department of Justice and Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) investigated and accused a group of civil rights leaders, including New Black Panthers Huey Newton, John T. Sidinger, and Medgar Evers, of plotting a “violent overthrow” of President Barack Obama.\n\n“I think what we can say about the release"}
{"prompt": "Nysius huttoni\n\nNysius huttoni, the wheat bug, is a species of seed bug", "expected": ", an insect in the family Lygaeidae. It was formerly endemic to New Zealand, but was introduced to Europe, including", "actual": " found in Europe (the Czech Republic and the Baltic nations), the Alps of Europe, and southern Russia. There are two subspecies. The nominate subspecies Nysius huttoni huttoni lives mainly in Europe, the Alps, and the Russian Caucasus, and there are no records of the second subspecies Nysius huttoni vorosi in the Russian Caucasus. This species can be considered \"vulnerable\" with known populations <20,000.\n\nDescription\nNysius huttoni has a body length of 5.3 millimeters, a body width of 6.5 millimeters,"}
{"prompt": "Numerical cognition\n\nNumerical cognition is a subdiscipline of cognitive science that studies the cognitive, developmental and", "expected": " neural bases of numbers and mathematics. As with many cognitive science endeavors, this is a highly interdisciplinary topic, and includes researchers", "actual": " behavioural aspects of numerical representation and its relationship to other cognitive domains. It is primarily concerned with the development of numerical skill and the neural correlates of numerical cognition.\n\nCognitive development\n\nStudies of numerical cognition have focused on children aged three to four, in whom numerical ability emerges and is further developed from an early age. The earliest evidence of preschool numerical cognition comes from studies of non-standard number-related behaviour in children aged one year three to four. These children demonstrated greater sensitivity to the number of the objects they touched or manipulated with their fingers, relative to the number of the objects they saw or handled. In the"}
{"prompt": "1945 in Norway\n\nEvents in the year 1945 in Norway.\n\nIncumbents\nGovernment in Exile (in London", "expected": ") until 9 May\n Monarch – Haakon VII\n Prime Minister – Johan Nygaardsvold (Labour Party", "actual": " and other British overseas territories under German occupation) from Norway\nVacant (until 7 June)\nLabour Party (until 18 June)\n\nEvents\n\n \nNorway\n1945 \nNorway\nCategory:Years of the 20th century in Norway\nCategory:1945 in Europe\nCategory:1945 in Norway"}
{"prompt": "\"NARRATOR:\" \"In the criminal justice system the people are represented by two separate yet equally important groups, the police", "expected": " who investigate crime and the district attorneys who prosecute the offenders.\" \"These are their stories.\" \"(SIREN WAILING", "actual": " who investigate crime and the district attorneys who prosecute the offenders.\" \"These are their stories.\" \"We have just about a minute before we need to talk.\" \"I got a pretty good feeling about this little lady.\" \"HANK:\" \"Well, don't get any ideas.\" \"JOHNSON:\" \"I got a pretty good feeling about this little lady.\" \"We're gonna get your money.\" \"You're gonna pay him, aren't you?\" \"Let's see how he's gonna pay you.\" \"You don't wanna do that.\" \"Take it easy.\" \"I thought people who robbed banks did"}
{"prompt": "XBOX Gamertag\n\nDiscord Username\n\nSteam ID\n\nHello, Everyone!\nWelcome to the first", "expected": " installment of Wildcard Workshop! Where I bring you tutorials, tips & tricks, and best practices for modding.\nToday", "actual": " Official Gamepad Thread!\nI'm sure many of us here will do our best to make you as comfortable in your new setup as possible!\nPlease note that Xbox will not be sending you a gamepad, so this thread is all about you, the Gamertag owner, being able to connect to your Xbox and use your controller with the included joysticks.\n\nMy gamertag is\n\"Gamertagname\"\nAnd my Xbox is\n\"XBOX\"\nMy controller is\n\"Xbox 360\"\nI'm very new to the Gamertag thing. I can't get into my"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nRails - Using an argument as a model attribute\n\nHere's my view:\n<%=", "expected": " check_box_tag :age_visible, 1, checked?(:age_visible) %>\n\nThis", "actual": " form_for @post, :html => { :multipart => true }, :url => { :controller => \"posts\", :action => \"add_post\" } do |f| %>\n  ...\n  <input type=\"hidden\" name=\"id\" value=<%= @post.id %>>\n  ...\n\nIn the controller I have:\n@post = Post.new\n@post.user_id = request.env[\"devise.mapping.database_for\"]\n@post.save!\n\nBut for a single post it works just fine"}
{"prompt": "25 Oct Seed Propagation of Cornus florida\n\nThe glossy red fruit, called a drupe, of", "expected": " Cornus florida is rapidly disappearing from our native dogwood. This fruit is a favorite of our feathered friends and", "actual": " a Cornus florida, native to the southeastern and north-central United States and Canada, is commonly called a Corn Flakes. It contains cyanogenic glucosides. Corn seed contains cyanogenic glucosides. The blue star of the corn plant resembles a blue or violet aster. It has a distinctive odor of sweet mint with a hint of orange. The plant is used as an herbal remedy for its anti-flatulent effect and other digestive and respiratory disorders. Cabbage and Kiamsuke, the purple-red cabbagelike plant, are also commonly called corn. Cabbage, one of the earliest domest"}
{"prompt": "// Code generated by protoc-gen-gogo.\n// source: empty.proto\n// DO NOT EDIT", "expected": "!\n\n/*\nPackage types is a generated protocol buffer package.\n\nIt is generated from these files:\n\t", "actual": "!\n\n/*\n\tPackage empty is a generated protocol buffer package.\n\n\tIt is generated from these files:\n\t\tempty.proto\n\n\tIt has these top-level messages:\n\t\tEmpty\n\t\tXXX_InternalExtensions\n*/\npackage empty\n\nimport proto \"github.com/gogo/protobuf/proto\"\nimport fmt \"fmt\"\nimport math \"math\"\nimport _ \"github.com/gogo/protobuf/gogoproto\"\n\nimport io \"io\"\n\n// Reference imports to suppress"}
{"prompt": "Busseron Township, Knox County, Indiana\n\nBusseron Township is one of ten townships in Knox", "expected": " County, Indiana. As of the 2010 census, its population was 1,393 and it contained 618 housing units.\n", "actual": " County, Indiana, United States. As of the 2010 census, its population was 1,818 and it contained 673 housing units.\n\nGeography\nAccording to the 2010 census, the township has a total area of , of which  (or 99.91%) is land and  (or 0.093%) is water.\n\nCities, towns, villages\n Busseron\n\nUnincorporated towns\n Bussietown at \n(This list is based on USGS data and may include former settlements.)\n\nCemeteries\nThe township contains these five cem"}
{"prompt": "Thalassemia Minor and Major: Current Management.\nThalassemia is a common genetic disorder. It has been", "expected": " estimated that in India nearly 5 crore people are thalassemia carriers. They are asymptomatic and are detected on", "actual": " estimated that between 0.15 and 0.25% of the world's population is affected. In addition, thalassemia is responsible for a significant proportion of deaths of newborns and young children in the United States. Approximately 2,000 infants are born annually with severe transfusion-dependent beta-thalassemia major. This condition results in a reduced number of erythrocytes in the blood and a deficiency in the production of hemoglobin A, which is a major component of erythrocyte cells. Patients who survive this disorder are usually affected with milder variants. Although many patients with severe th"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nPandas \"join\" oddity\n\nIf I try this (with two different vintages of", "expected": " pandas, one in Python 2, another in Python 3)\nimport pandas as pd\nx = pd", "actual": " pandas):\nimport pandas as pd\n\ndf1 = pd.DataFrame(dict(A=pd.Series(data), B=pd.Series(data2), \n   C=pd.Series(data3), D=pd.Series(data4)))\n\ndf2 = pd.DataFrame(dict(A=pd.Series(data5), B=pd.Series(data6), \n   C=pd.Series(data7), D=pd.Series(data8)))\n\nthen I get:\ndf1."}
{"prompt": "Hypoglycemia in diabetes: pathophysiological mechanisms and diurnal variation.\nIatrogenic hypoglycemia", "expected": ", the limiting factor in the glycemic management of diabetes, causes recurrent morbidity (and sometimes death), precludes maintenance of", "actual": " is a frequent complication in diabetes. Recent studies have demonstrated a strong association between the severity of the hypoglycemic episode and an increased postprandial hyperinsulinemia, and a concomitantly increased risk of all-cause and cardiovascular mortality. However, the pathophysiology of iatrogenic hypoglycemia in diabetes is still incompletely understood. Recent data, using the hyperinsulinemic-euglycemic clamp technique, have suggested that insulin resistance plays an important role in the pathophysiology of iatrogenic hypoglycemia in type 1 diabetes, and has also become evident"}
{"prompt": "/**\n * Tencent is pleased to support the open source community by making QMUI_iOS available.\n * Copyright", "expected": " (C) 2016-2020 THL A29 Limited, a Tencent company. All rights reserved.\n * Licensed under", "actual": " (C) 2016-2020 THL A29 Limited, a Tencent company. All rights reserved.\n * Licensed under the MIT License (the \"License\"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n * http://opensource.org/licenses/MIT\n * Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations"}
{"prompt": "Maturation of pig oocytes: observations on membrane potential.\nThe membrane-potential changes of pig oocytes during m", "expected": "aturation are described. Cumulus-enclosed oocytes have a resting potential of -41.81 +/- 0.60 m", "actual": "aturation were studied by membrane potential difference, extracellular, and intracellular recordings. Two groups of matured oocytes were studied, one with a high GV (GVH) and the other with a low GV (GVL). In both the groups, low-voltage (low-V) oocytes (GVH) (n = 9) and high-voltage (high-V) oocytes (GVL) (n = 6) showed progressive declines of the membrane potential, with a significant (P less than 0.01) difference (from 2 to 5 days after inse"}
{"prompt": "//\n// Copyright 2020 The AMP HTML Authors. All Rights Reserved.\n//\n// Licensed under the Apache License,", "expected": " Version 2.0 (the \"License\");\n// you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n", "actual": " Version 2.0 (the \"License\");\n// you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n// You may obtain a copy of the License at\n//\n//      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n//\n// Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n// distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS-IS\" BASIS,\n// WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\n// See the License for the specific language governing"}
{"prompt": "\"\"\"PyUnit testing that threads honor our signal semantics\"\"\"\n\nimport unittest\nimport signal\nimport os\nimport", "expected": " sys\nfrom test.support import run_unittest, import_module\nthread = import_module('_thread", "actual": " sys\nimport time\n\nimport pytest\n\n# Import sys, os, and threading modules so we won't have to write the same tests\n# twice.\nsys_path = os.getenv(\"PYTHONPATH\", \"\") if have_unix else []\nsys_thread = os.getenv(\"PYTHONSTACKNAME\", \"\") if have_unix else []\nsys_platform = os.getenv(\"PYTHONPLATFORM\", \"\")\nos.mkdir(\".\", exist_ok=True)\nos.mkdir"}
{"prompt": "An unique n-propyl sesquiterpene from Eryngium creticum L. (Api", "expected": "aceae).\nThe unique 1-n-propyl-perhydronaphthaline 1,2,4a,", "actual": "aceae).\nSeven new sesquiterpenoids, 6alpha-hydroxy-2beta,3beta-secolabd-11-en-8alpha-ol (1), 6alpha/beta-hydroxy-2beta,3beta-secolabd-10(17),12(16)-dien-8alpha,5alpha,12beta-triol (2), 6alpha-hydroxy-2beta,3beta-secolabd-11-en-8alpha-ol (3), 6alpha-hydroxy-3beta,11-epoxy"}
{"prompt": "The Los Angeles LGBT Center offers nearly every service imaginable: medical care, affordable housing, homeless shelters, legal services, employment services", "expected": ", cultural events, a charter high school, and advocacy for the entire LGBT community. Their seven locations across Los Angeles offer more", "actual": ", free legal assistance, and a 24-hour crisis center. This service is so critical to a vulnerable population that, for a time now, the Los Angeles LGBT Center has been a hub for the movement against Proposition 8, the ballot initiative that overturned the state's marriage equality law. And when supporters of Proposition 8 realized that the LGBT Center was hosting the event to repeal the Proposition, they decided to hold it at the center. (The group who originally created the event moved that night to a different venue, but the event was held on February 20, 2009.) For almost five weeks, organizers struggled to keep the event on"}
{"prompt": "<!DOCTYPE html>\r\n<html>\r\n\r\n<head>\r\n\t<title", "expected": ">Wicket Examples's JS tests</title>\r\n\t<meta http-equiv=\"content-type\" content", "actual": ">Итальянские кнопки Земли и Тихонимы</title>\r\n\t<meta name=\"robots\" content=\"noindex,nofollow\" />\r\n\t<meta name=\"googlebot\" content=\"noindex,nofollow\" />\r\n\t<meta name=\"viewport\" content=\"width=device-width\" />\r\n\t<meta name=\"apple-mobile-web-app-capable\" content=\"yes\" />\r\n"}
{"prompt": "train = [\n    \"host-a011-lidar0-12358667072990650", "expected": "96-1235866732198912176\",\n    \"host-a011-lidar0-", "actual": "-18\",\n    \"host-a011-lidar0-20336744755989078-18\",\n    \"host-a011-lidar0-203056118907750164-18\",\n    \"host-a011-lidar0-20304697859223699-18\",\n    \"host-a011-lidar0-135957881426248033-18\",\n    \"host-a011-lidar0-"}
{"prompt": "package com.yingjun.ssm.dao;\r\n\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.", "expected": "entity.Goods;\r\nimport org.apache.ibatis.annotations.Param;\r\n\r\nimport", "actual": "bean.AppInfo;\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.bean.ContactInfo;\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.bean.GroupInfo;\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.bean.LinkInfo;\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.bean.MessageInfo;\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.bean.MusicVideoInfo;\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.constants.AppType;\r\nimport com.yingjun.ssm.constants.AppTypeEnum;\r\nimport"}
{"prompt": "\"English subtitle by aesc 2015 ;).\" \" Look, it's a chamber.\" \" Yeah, I see.\" \" Go", "expected": " on.\" \" Get off my foot, would you?\" \"Go on.\" \"Do you see anything?\" \"Spiders.\"", "actual": ".\" \"Go on.\" \" What did you see?\" \" I saw something.\" \" What did you see?\" \" I saw the woman.\" \"You were looking for the chamber.\" \"That's what we'd been trying to find.\" \"There's something in here.\" \" There is?\" \" Yeah.\" \"And you know what?\" \"There's nothing wrong with it.\" \"It's just a chamber.\" \"A what?\" \"How do you know?\" \"Look under it.\" \"Okay, take the flashlight.\" \"Put it in there.\" \"What are you doing?\" \"Oh, Jesus!\" \" What are you"}
{"prompt": "Trouble logging in?If you can't remember your password or are having trouble logging in, you will have to reset", "expected": " your password. If you have trouble resetting your password (for example, if you lost access to the original email address),", "actual": " your password. If you have trouble resetting your password (for example, if you lost access to the original email address), please do not start posting with a new account, as this is against the forum rules. If you create a temporary account, please contact us right away via Forum Support, and send us any information you can about your original account, such as the account name and any email address that may have been associated with it.\n\nThis post contains spoilers for the episode aired in Japan on the 26th.\n\nAs I was typing this, I remembered something off the top of my head: this is"}
{"prompt": "// mkerrors.sh -m64\n// Code generated by the command above; see README.md. DO", "expected": " NOT EDIT.\n\n// +build amd64,solaris\n\n// Code generated by cmd/cgo -", "actual": " NOT EDIT.\n\n// +build arm64,netbsd\n\n// Code generated by cmd/cgo -godefs; DO NOT EDIT.\n// cgo -godefs -- -m64 _const.go\n\npackage unix\n\nimport \"syscall\"\n\nconst (\n\tAF_APPLETALK                      = 0x10\n\tAF_ARP                      "}
{"prompt": "function a() {}\n", "expected": "", "actual": "\nvar b = {\n\ta: a,\n\tb: a\n};\n\nvar c = {\n\ta: b,\n\tb: b\n};\n\nvar d = {\n\ta: b,\n\tb: b\n};\n\nvar e = {\n\ta: b,\n\tb: a\n};\n\nvar f = {\n\ta: a,\n\tb: c\n};\n\nvar g = {\n\ta: f,\n\tb: b\n};\n\nvar h = {\n\ta: b,\n\tb: c\n};\n\nvar i = {\n\ta: f,\n"}
{"prompt": "Established in 1887 as part of L.A.'s first official suburb, Angelino Heights, Carroll Avenue is famous", "expected": " for having the largest concentration of Victorian-era homes in the city, and the highest concentration of Eastlake and Queen Anne residences", "actual": " for its large, single-family residences. In the early 1900s, a streetcar line bypassed South Central L.A., and Angelino Heights' streetcar stop was replaced by a stoplight. In the 1930s, residents rallied to save Carroll Avenue from a new freeway (now Interstate 5), which would have reduced the enclave to a mere 15-block length of street grid. Carroll Avenue is still beautiful, home to more than a dozen Victorian and Edwardian homes (and a recently-redesigned, 1930s-style building that is part of a large residential complex). Some believe that the district was designed to"}
{"prompt": "Four Score\n\nFour-Star Dining at 4am\n\nDaylight Savings. For one magical night, you and", "expected": " the hard stuff will have 60 glorious extra minutes\ntogether. After which you’ll be feeling especially peckish.", "actual": " a date can get up and go while your neighbors sleep. You’ll hear their alarm clocks go off in the morning.\n\nIt’s been a full decade since Congress repealed the law that mandated daylight savings, allowing states to decide — and often vote against — what time their clocks move forward. Now some states are returning to some of the country’s earliest changes to the time-keeping.\n\nIf you’re in the South, you’re probably not celebrating. Georgia and South Carolina are the latest states voting to move ahead with their original time-change scheme.\n\n"}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThis invention relates to novel amphoteric starch derivatives and their application as wet-end additives for", "expected": " improving both wet and dry strength of paper.\n2. Description of the Prior Art\nCommercial wet-strength paper additives,", "actual": " paper and photographic paper.\n2. Description of the Prior Art\nPhthalic-functional starch derivatives having an amino group or a carboxyl group at the 2-position have been known as wet-end additives for various paper products. Such derivatives, however, are not satisfactory owing to their high hydrophilicity and insufficient compatibility with the main constituent resins and wet-end additives used in paper making.\nIn contrast, cationic amphoteric starch derivatives having an amino group or a carboxyl group at the 2-position are superior in compatibility with the conventional wet-end additives. Their use,"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nMS Access form gets broken after enabling unsafe content\n\nI have a MS Access project, which was developed", "expected": " in MS Access 97. I successfully converted it to MS Access 2016 (that was a long story tho). Everything looks fine,", "actual": " by another programmer.\nI've just recently noticed the MS Access forms keep getting broken.\nFirst of all, I've not done anything like that before, so I'm not sure why this is happening.\nAlso, I think I've found the problem:\nThe unsafe content in the form are of type \"TextEdit\", but this should be fine (I've set up a form to only show text fields of type TextBox).\nAnyway, when I disable all the unsafe content (in the form), and re-enable all the unsafe content (in the form), the form gets again broken.\nI"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nSignalR freezing all subsequent http requests\n\nI am trying to use SignalR in my web application", "expected": " and it is hosted on IIS 7.5.\nI am using Windows 7 X64 (without SP1) and", "actual": ". One thing I've observed is that when I make ajax calls using SignalR, the SignalR will freeze for all subsequent calls to the webapp. This only happens when SignalR is setuid to the http context's userId. When I set UserId to a random id and then set SignalRUID to the same id, all data is able to be pushed to the client.\nTo reproduce the issue, follow the below steps.\n\nCreate a new C# ASP.NET, Web-API 2.0 project\nAdd a new folder named as “ChatServer”"}
{"prompt": "[Use of the variation pulsimetry in the evaluation of diurnal dynamics of cardiac rhythm in patients with ischemic heart", "expected": " disease and functional disorders of the cardiovascular system].\nThe results of employing the method of variation pulsimetry and dynamic electrocard", "actual": " disease].\nPulsimetric alterations in the ECG (PEL) provide additional information on the frequency stability of cardiac rhythm. It is also recognized that PEL represents a reliable tool in the assessment of the ischemic heart disease (IHD). An important problem in the analysis of PEL and its significance for the assessment of the heart rhythm in patients with IHD is the lack of standardization of the analysis. This paper presents the development of an analytical method and its application for quantitative evaluation of the PEL and investigation of its significance in the assessment of heart rhythm in patients with IHD. The proposed mathematical"}
{"prompt": "Borrowing the popular idea from the NFL Network, The Times-Picayune's New Orleans Saints coverage team came up", "expected": " with our ranking of the top 25 players on the Saints' roster heading into the 2012 season. The idea is to make these", "actual": " with an \"enhanced\" version of \"The Ringer\" post game show for Sunday night's game.\n\nIf you weren't watching the game, the show was pretty good. I'm not saying it's the best show or anything, but it did get most of the facts right. I'm just saying it was a good effort.\n\nIf you weren't watching the game, the show was pretty good. I'm not saying it's the best show or anything, but it did get most of the facts right. I'm just saying it was a good effort.\n\nClick to expand...\n"}
{"prompt": "Oliver Heldens\n\nOlivier J. L. Heldens (born February 1, 1995), better known by", "expected": " his stage name Oliver Heldens, is a Dutch DJ and electronic music producer from Rotterdam. He is regarded as a", "actual": " his stage name Oliver Heldens, is a Dutch DJ and singer-songwriter, who was born in Hilversum but moved to Suriname from the Netherlands when he was 3 years old. He grew up in Sint Maarten and moved to Curaçao and the Dutch islands of St Maarten and Sint Eustatius once he turned 14.\n\nHedelens made his musical debut in 2008, with the song \"Giganten\", released on his own label, T2O Music, and later on iTunes. He went on to release three singles, \"Sleeping"}
{"prompt": "Een 14-jarige jongen die maandagochtend zwaargewond raakte door e", "expected": "en aanrijding met een auto is aan zijn verwondingen bezweken, me", "actual": "en grote schilderij, is ontslagen voor een huisartsen zaak. Dat komt volgens het federaal parket doordat er geen sprake was van een gewonde bewoner.\n\nDe man was op dat moment op de weg naar zijn werkzaamheden aan de Aare voorzien van een rond lachweeb met plasten die hij naar zichzelf toe had gekregen.\n\nDe man is zwa"}
{"prompt": "Rethymno Cretan Kings B.C.\n\nRethymno Cretan Kings B.C", "expected": "., or simply Cretan Kings (Greek: Ρέθυμνο Κρ�", "actual": ". (Cypro-Cretans: Ρόθε) is a Cypriot professional basketball team that is based in Rethymno, Crete that plays in the Cypriot League. The team played its home games in Panarea Gialaraki (Panarea Stadium) until the 2010–11 season. The team plays its home games in the Rethymno Municipal Stadium.\n\nHistory\n\nCrete\nThe Rethymno Cretan Kings B.C. (Ρόθε/Ρόθε Cretan"}
{"prompt": "For three years Michael Fucito has been buried deep in the Seattle Sounders depth charts behind numerous star strikers, seeing very limited", "expected": " time on the field. In the Third Round Tuesday night he made his US Open Cup debut and scored both Sounders goals in a", "actual": " playing time under his previous club. But as a member of the team’s Academy, Fucito is set to receive a chance to earn a starting spot in USL League One this season.\n\nThis past weekend, Fucito participated in his first training sessions with the Sounders, and he’s been living out of a suitcase for the past three months. He says the experience has been both enjoyable and enlightening.\n\nFucito, who can play in central midfield, central defense, or right back, is one of a number of academy players who’ve had to play for their"}
{"prompt": "871 F.2d 179\n50 Fair Empl.Prac.Cas.  971,49 Empl", "expected": ". Prac. Dec. P 38,882, 13 Fed.R.Serv.3d 330\nThomasina M", "actual": ". Prac. Dec. P 38,738, 55 USLW 2084\nDELAWARE VALLEY TURNPIKE AUTHORITY, Appellant,v.WOMAN'S HOSPITALS OF AMERICA, INC., Appellee.\nNo. 88-1564.\nUnited States Court of Appeals,Third Circuit.\nArgued Oct. 30, 1988.Decided April 15, 1989.\n\nWilliam S. Robinson (argued), James W. Schlesinger, Robinson, Brog & Baker, Charlotte, N.C., Thomas F. Murphy, Robinson"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nClosed as not constructive?\n\nCan someone explain why my question was not constructive?\nhttps://", "expected": "softwareengineering.stackexchange.com/questions/187264/how-do-i-take-", "actual": "politics.stackexchange.com/questions/1475/is-the-war-on-drugs-the-first-war-against-the-poor\nTo me it seems like an important analysis that could be useful to other readers who might be interested in the same topic.\nI am not trying to be controversial or offend the mods of this site. I am just asking for a good analysis. Would the community be willing to weigh in on the matter?\nEDIT: I have updated the post with a better analysis of the question after feedback from the mods.\n\nA:"}
{"prompt": "\nfixupOutputHooks+=(_linkDLLs)\n\n# For every *.{exe,dll}", "expected": " in $output/bin/ we try to find all (potential)\n# transitive dependencies and symlink those", "actual": " file in the list above, run the '-m' argument.\n# We use .dll here since that can be a bit easier to type than a .exe\n# extension.\nfixupOutputHooks+=('-m .dll')\n\n# Find the files from the list in directory 'debug'\ndebugHooks=(\n  $(patsubst %-f,%.obj-*-*,[-h .],$(filter %.obj-*-* %.obj-*-*.obj-*,[))\n)\n\n# Get the DLL name and"}
{"prompt": "Rutland-7 Vermont Representative District, 2002–12\n\nThe Rutland-7 Representative District is a one member", "expected": " state Representative district in the U.S. state of Vermont.  It is one of the 108 one or two member districts", "actual": " congressional district in the U.S. state of Vermont.  It is currently represented by Democrat Paul H. Dunphy of Charlotte.\n\nThe district contains all of Rutland County and portions of the towns of Windham, St. Albans, and Rutland City.\n\nRecent election results from presidential races:\n\nHistorical and current district boundaries\n\nGovernment\nThe district is fully in the 9th State Senate District, which is in the 11th State Senate District and is represented by Susan M. McCarroll (R).\n\nThe district is made up of parts of the following municipalities:"}
{"prompt": "Forget about the well-deserved break this December school holiday. Parents are signing up their children for study boot camps to", "expected": " get a head start in the academic rat race.\n\nSome turn up for such hothousing sessions, hoping to guarantee", "actual": " cram their brains to bursting point with a whirlwind amount of information. With more than 50,000 students taking part in the classes, University College Dublin is hoping to build a reputation for delivering the most intense and comprehensive training available to parents and students.\n\nThe training is only a month long and will see students studying for their first exam, A-level. It offers a “two-year crash course in studying for A level”. A-levels are notoriously difficult to get right and they involve high-level thinking and writing.\n\nThis training is designed to ensure students get the best marks possible. From"}
{"prompt": "After five and a half days of hearing from multiple witnesses and viewing dramatic photos and videos, a Stamford, Conn., jury of", "expected": " six awarded Mary Margaret Farren $28.6 million.\n\nFarren filed a civil suit against her ex-husband", "actual": " six men and six women handed down a guilty verdict of second-degree murder in the 2012 killing of Kevin O’Connor in a downtown Stamford parking lot.\n\nIt was the culmination of a two-month trial, which included testimony from police officers, DNA analysis of DNA evidence, and eyewitness testimony.\n\nJurors took two hours and 55 minutes to deliberate before arriving at their decision, rejecting the defense’s arguments that O’Connor’s death was accidental and that his drug-induced coma contributed to his death.\n\n\nThe defense tried the case based on circumstantial evidence and"}
{"prompt": "Newsroom\n\nTreasurer Lynn Fitch and College Savings Mississippi Giving Out Over $3150 in MACS Scholarships", "expected": "\n\nPosted On:\n5/16/2018\n\nNewsroomArticle\n\nJackson, MS. Treasurer Lynn F", "actual": "\n\nOctober 25, 2019\n\nMACS’ Dr. Elizabeth King is pleased to let you know about the $3250 in scholarships offered through the University of Southern Mississippi’s College Savings Mississippi Giving program.\n\nThe scholarships are scholarships given to Mississippi high school seniors to help pay for college.\n\n“In fact, this year we’ve increased the scholarship amount to help students who are interested in furthering their education,” said Professor King. “Our students work hard preparing for finals, so the college scholarships that MACS offers now help them reach their dreams and build their"}
{"prompt": "Keeping up with all your contacts can be tough. People move, change their phone numbers, and otherwise outdate your address book", "expected": " all the time. Free service WriteThat.Name keeps your Gmail address book always up-to-date by scanning incoming email", "actual": ". This is one of the reasons why an email address book can be such a valuable tool for your business.\n\nHowever, there are a few things that you need to consider so that you can make the most of your email address book.\n\nYour email address book is a tool, not a must-have.\n\nFor some businesses, their email address books are a must-have. For others, email accounts come with default addresses.\n\nThe solution is simple: use the default email addresses and create a separate one that’s personal.\n\nYou can use a default email address if you"}
{"prompt": "It took Djokovic four French Open finals to win his first. After the match, he was asked what went through his", "expected": " mind on championship point, and he talked about his “connection” with the people at Roland Garros. There it", "actual": " mind during those four days.\n\n\"I was actually feeling really great,\" he said. \"I was not hitting any bad shots. It was a really good feeling. But then, as the match went on, it got a little bit harder. The first two rounds I was really feeling really good. I wasn't hitting a bad shot all day. Then the third round, I felt like I was holding my serve. And then that fourth day, I was feeling like I was having trouble taking my first shots off the baseline because it was almost like a mental thing. I couldn't hit my groundstroke. It"}
{"prompt": "In every other post, Kang Hye Jung stocks what seems like a screenshot from the Pokémon Go app taken at an Epik", "expected": " Top concert with Pikachu conspicuously status on level amongstthe remainder of the Epik High members.", "actual": " High School. This one shows the school being attacked by a Pokémon Go-themed villain.\n\n\nIn the game, Pokémons (pokémon) and Pokémon creatures (pikachu) roam around towns and cities in order to battle one another, and earn money and various rewards. It's not just a game you can play in your backyard with your kids for a while, but one that's going to change the way you interact with your world. It all started in New York City, and the results have been nothing short of amazing, not just for cities around the world, but for life in general.\n\n"}
{"prompt": "#lang pyret\n\nprovide *\nimport error as E\n\ncheck:\n  string-char-at", "expected": "(\"\", 0) raises \"index\"\n  string-char-at(\"a\", -1) raises \"index\"", "actual": ":\n    check:\n      +1: {E.error, \"string literal can't be used as a literal with character indexing\"}\n      0: {}\n      '': {}\n\n  literal-char-at:\n    check:\n      +1: {E.error, \"string literal can't be used as a literal with pattern matching\"}\n      0: {}\n      '': {}\n\n  literal-byte-at:\n  "}
{"prompt": "This title was originally released as Rubik’s Cube, but the name was changed we assume for licensing reasons. Atari", "expected": " Video Cube is the easier version to find. It was initially available only to Atari Club members through the Atari Age magazine, but", "actual": " games usually came with a manual or even a box; not that many of these exist anymore. This is the manual of the Rubik’s Cube from the Atari 5200, featuring “The Computer Aided Rubik’s Cube Solver” written by John R. Pierce.\n\nThis is an amazing hand written paper which describes the creation of the 5200. It was originally created by John R. Pierce. On the bottom of each page is a legend, showing the game’s history and being an attempt to describe all of the key points of the development. The most important of"}
{"prompt": "Top Ten Boating Lakes\nWhen it comes to boating there are plenty of lakes that allow you to have fun. However", "expected": ", there are few lakes that are the best for boating and you should take advantage of the fun these lakes have to offer", "actual": ", sometimes you have to remember when thinking of which lakes you want to use for your boat that do not have any problems.\n\n1. The Lake of St. John\nThe Lake of St. John is a beautiful lake with the highest water levels you can find at a lake. You should put your boat in the lake during the summer so the water becomes calm. You will see a wide variety of scenery in the lake from green water and trees along with colorful houses and houses with people, and animals will be found in this lake on most days of the week.\n\n2. Lake George\nLake George is"}
{"prompt": "2016–17 Alashkert FC season\n\nThe 2016–17 season was Alashkert's 4th season", "expected": " in the Armenian Premier League and 8th overall. Alashkert defended their Premier League title having won it the previous seasons", "actual": " in the Azerbaijan Premier League, the top-tier football league of Azerbaijan. They participated in the Azerbaijan Premier League and UEFA Champions League qualifying rounds.\n\nBackground\n\nKhoriv-Almas Shahidzadeh was appointed as the club's new manager on 9 May 2017. He was replaced by Zaur Džukanov.\n\nFirst-team squad\n\nOut on loan\n\nTransfers\n\nIn\n\nTotal spending:  30,000 euro\n\nTotal income:  20,000 euro\n\nOut\n\nTotal income:  15,000 euro\n\n"}
{"prompt": "Swarthmore's independent campus newspaper since 1881\n\nWhat I Won’t Miss about Swat: Ref", "expected": "lections Before leaving for the Summer\n\nAh, summer, so close and yet so far. Various seedy “moving", "actual": "lections on the Class of ’06\n\nIt’s not easy to write about Swat. Even the most casual observer might pause at a point when he realizes just how little the place stands in the public memory, how many people know, or care, that it exists.\n\nSwarthsville is an odd place, and a particularly unlikely one for a university to call home. It was founded in 1895 by Colonel Arthur Swarthout, a Tennessee native who had been enamored of the idea of an exclusively black school for his son. But he did not have the financial resources he needed to"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nHow can I get access to the items within \"this\"\n\nHow can I get access to the", "expected": " items within \"this\" so that I can chain further elements onto a \"this\" object?\nI am sure I am", "actual": " items within \"this\"\nThis is what I have\nvar arr = this.value.split(';');\nif (arr.length > 1) {\n  for (i = 0; i < arr.length; i++) {\n    var split = arr[i].split(':');\n    if (split.length == 2) {\n      var x = {\n        x: split[0],\n        y: split[1]\n      }\n\n "}
{"prompt": "Priming race in biracial observers affects visual search for Black and White faces.\nWe examined whether or not priming racial", "expected": " identity would influence Black-White biracial individuals' ability to visually search for White and Black faces. Black, White, and", "actual": " information in the form of a single face cue altered the visual search process in nonrace--biased observers. We manipulated the visual system-wide priming of racial information (a prime race priming (Pr prime) or a single-face prime prime (SF prime)) in the visual search task and used the findings to provide a more robust test of the racial bias hypothesis. Three experiments were conducted. Experiment 1 was a color-alone search task, and Experiment 2 was a color-color search task. In Experiment 2, all participants underwent face-alone search as a baseline for the non-face primes. The results"}
{"prompt": "Variation in performance in low-volume mammography screening programmes: experience from Switzerland.\nReading volume and mammography screening performance", "expected": " appear positively correlated. Quality and effectiveness were compared across low-volume screening programmes targeting relatively small populations and operating under the same decentral", "actual": " of the Swiss screening programme were examined after introduction of the organised reading programme and with a lower level of coverage. Screening results from the national programme were compared with results of screening programmes in other parts of Switzerland. The coverage for screening was not modified in the Swiss programme. Screening performance in the Swiss programme has been significantly influenced by changes in the distribution of women over the age of 50 who are invited for screening; the screening performance was improved after the introduction of the organised reading programme, without substantial changes in the performance of the other programmes. The Swiss programme reached only 62% of its target and could be considered as one of"}
{"prompt": "Blackwood\n\nI dig. It's what I do. I'll literally use a shovel to answer a question. Some", "expected": " answers, though, have been buried too deep for too long. But I'll find those, too. And I know where", "actual": " questions are more than one sentence. Some are two sentences. Others are three sentences. We really don't care, other than to get the right answer. But others are as long as ten sentences.\n\n\"How many syllables per word?\"\n\n\"How many syllables per line?\"\n\n\"How much do you hate that line, and why?\"\n\n\"How much is more than twice as fast as the fastest of the first set?\"\n\n\"How many times are there enough syllables to make 10 sentences?\"\n\n\"How many words per line?\"\n\n\"How many words per"}
{"prompt": "Author: David Waldman\n\nDavid Waldman is a film writer, cinematographer, director, producer, actor,", "expected": " editor and composer. In addition, he is an unsigned singer/songwriter/arranger/performer with numerous original songs", "actual": " writer and journalist. He is the author of “Filmography: A History of Silent Film’s 100 Greatest Short Films” and “The Complete Guide to Silent Film Sound” and “The Complete Guide to Silent Film Editing.” He has written and produced for numerous television shows including “The Sopranos,” “The Good Wife,” “The Bridge,” “The Mentalist,” “Klaus and the Showgirl,” “Dennis Miller” and “One Tree Hill.” He won the"}
{"prompt": "SURVIVING SUPER BOMBS IN ROBLOX!!!!\n▶ Subscribe - http://bit.ly/", "expected": "10361uv\n▶ Twitter - https://twitter.com/Bigbst4tz2\n▶ Instagram -", "actual": "WOWSub\n♂ Donate - http://bit.ly/WOWDonate\n▶ Discord - http://bit.ly/WOWDiscord\n♂ Twitter - http://bit.ly/WOWTwitter\n♂ Facebook - http://bit.ly/WOWFacebook\n▶ Twitch - http://bit.ly/WOWTwitch\n♂ Instagram - http://bit.ly/wogam\n🕊 Want to support me? - https://www.patreon.com/wobama\n⭐ The WOW Project - http://bit"}
{"prompt": "Pharmacological characterization of endomorphin-2-based cyclic pentapeptides with methylated phenylalanine", "expected": " residues.\nAs part of our continuing studies on the structure-activity relationships of cyclic pentapeptides based on the", "actual": " has been reported previously, in which the endomorphin-2 pharmacophore was characterized by comparing the binding affinities (pKi) of endomorphin-2 peptides with or without methylated phenylalanine (methyl-EtPhe or mEtPhe).^[@ref1],[@ref2]^ Methylated phenylalanine is known to occupy the Γ-loop of the η^6^-methylhistidine motif in opioid peptides, although this interaction is quite weak compared to other interactions with the γ-phosphate. We"}
{"prompt": "Square Wood Coffee Table – Making a wooden pallet coffee table is within everyone’s reach. Recycling some wooden", "expected": " pallets allows combining economy and ecology. With a little imagination and a few hours of crafts, you get a table that is", "actual": " pallets is one way to reuse these wood material. The wooden pallets are readily available in large quantities and can be recycled easily at any home decor. One of the best part is that these pallets can be collected easily without any hassles. They can easily be collected from many places, for example, from the building sites, construction sites, from dumpsters and many more. To recycle wooden pallets, you will need to have some experience in wood recycling.\n\nWood pallets are quite cheap and easily available in most of the markets and many home decor. These pallets can be used in many household"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nSQL Server Configuration Manager changes effected via Central Management Server\n\nWhen using Central Management Server (CMS),", "expected": " under Central Management Server Actions, SQL Server Configuration Manager (SSCM) is an option.\n\nWhen launched, the GUI", "actual": " with SQL Server 2000, SQL Server 2008, and SQL Server 2014, the Configuration Manager settings are applied to all SQL Server instances in the same database.\nHowever, if SQL Server is running under a different instance (say one that is running on Windows Server 2008), Configuration Manager settings are not applied.\nIn the following, we will show the steps needed to replicate these changes.\nStep 1: Update SQL Server 2012 Configuration Manager (CMS)\nOn the same Windows Server 2008 R2 Standard installation machine with SQL Server 2012, open the \"SQLSERVER\" folder and locate the following files:\n\n"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nDjango filter datetime base on date only\n\nI'm trying to filter the query set in", "expected": " the BaseDatatableView on a date that's entered in by the user in the following format: mm/dd/yy", "actual": " my Django view by only a date field. My data structure looks like this:\nclass ActivityHistoryEntry(models.Model):\n    entry_date = models.DateTimeField(auto_now=True)\n    user = models.ForeignKey(User)\n    activity_type = models.CharField(max_length=200,default=\"\")\n    created_at = models.DateTimeField(auto_now_add=True)\n\nI've tried to filter on the date field in my view by using a filter like this:\n"}
{"prompt": "sure it was known, or at least suspected but so long as it wasn't one of THEIR kids, it was evidently not", "expected": " a big concern. Sadly, covering for fellow doctors is something that's well known in medical circles.", "actual": " a crime. And those people who had the idea that it was the school's fault? Why? Because they never took any responsibility for their behavior. Why? Because THEY took no responsibility for anything.\n\n\"All right, there is a girl, but what do I tell her parents?\" I demanded.\n\nMrs. Johnson looked even more apologetic, but I didn't care. This was the most important thing to be done.\n\n\"Tell them I'm sorry. I never wanted to hurt them, and I never wanted the girls to be bullied.\"\n\n\"What did you think was going to"}
{"prompt": "'Catapulted into sexual health nursing leadership'.\nKevin Miles, nurse consultant and lead clinician for genitourinary", "expected": " medical services at Camden Primary Care Trust, explains why he feels he is in a position to lead evidence-based changes.", "actual": " medicine in NHS England, describes the work of Lister Hill Nursing in London during the COVID-19 pandemic. He explains how Lister Hill has adapted to the challenge, and how its staff have been able to be at the heart of the national response, with the focus on patient care, and not the virus itself. Kevin also reveals the story of how the team at Lister Hill led on the research surrounding the new COVID-19 diagnostic testing kit, so that it was developed in time to save lives, and also how this test could be used as a 'breathing tool' in the wider fight"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\npython: functions in class scope\n\nI am just playing around with the language, but wonder if it", "expected": " is possible to use functions defined within a scope of the class without explicitly defining self as the first argument.\nI understand the", "actual": " is possible to have a function in class scope, i.e. one that has local variables.\nclass A():\n    def m1(self, x, y):\n        return x*y\n\nclass B():\n    def m2(self, x, y):\n        self.m1(x,y)\n\nA()\nB()\n\nI get the error:\n\n<bound method A.m1 of <__main__.A instance at 0x0000025D5DC"}
{"prompt": "Evans, Eric M.\n\nEric M. Evans, age 69, went home to be with the Lord on Saturday", "expected": ", February 9, 2019. After fighting a courageous battle with ALS, he passed away peacefully, surrounded by his loving family.", "actual": " morning, on December 29, 2012.\n\nEric's son Mark was also present.\n\nHis funeral is Sunday morning at 11:30am in the Chapel of Rest, in Wausau.\n\nAt a previous time the service was at 10:00am.\n\nWe miss you Dad and love you all.\n\nPlease join us in the celebration of his life here in the Chapel of Rest today, October 29th, 2013 at 10:00 am.\n\nPrayer for the family:\nLord, thank You for Your eternal blessings. Please bring your strength to the mourners and"}
{"prompt": "# TinyUrl, version 3.8, for weechat version 0.3.0 or later\n#\n#", "expected": "   Listens to all channels for long URLs, and submits them to ln-s.net or\n#", "actual": " (c) 2007-2008 Chris Norland <chris@thecodebarbarian.org>\n#\n# Modified by Richard Knopper <r.knoppert@gmail.com> April 2009\n#  - Made \":x\" syntax optional\n#  - Added tab_width option\n#  - Renamed \":k\" to \":W\"\n#\n# Please keep in mind this file is public domain. No copyright assignment.\n# TinyUrl is distributed under the terms of the W3C License, with\n# permission for all uses, but not for modification"}
{"prompt": "Background {#Sec1}\n==========\n\nSevere equine asthma (sEA; previously known as recurrent air", "expected": "way obstruction) is a chronic disease of adult horses characterised by frequent coughing and increased respiratory effort at rest, as well as", "actual": "way disease) is the most severe phenotype of the group of equine respiratory diseases known as equine asthma and/or EAD (see Table [1](#Tab1){ref-type=\"table\"}). In the 1970s sEA was characterised as a syndrome with respiratory signs and lung function abnormalities that were caused by chronic, neutrophilic inflammatory processes of the lower airways \\[[@CR1]\\]. This syndrome occurs most frequently in horses aged between 1 month and 3 years. However, studies suggest that sEA may also affect adult and older horses \\[[@CR2]\\"}
{"prompt": "Prognostic impact of preoperative neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio in localized nonclear cell renal cell carcin", "expected": "oma.\nThe preoperative neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio was proposed as a prognostic factor for localized", "actual": "oma: a retrospective analysis of 547 patients.\nThe neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio (NLR) has been shown to be significantly associated with the prognoses of several different cancers. However, the precise prognostic impact of preoperative NLR on survival after surgical resection of localized, non-metastatic renal cell carcinoma (RCC) remains controversial. In this study, we investigated the prognostic impact of preoperative NLR in non-metastatic RCC patients undergoing surgical resection and analyzed the prognostic factors that affect the survival of surgery, either with or without"}
{"prompt": "\"One of the great disciples of the Buddha. Anuruddha was a cousin of the Buddha. Having often fallen asleep", "expected": " in the presence of the Buddha， he vowed one day that he would never sleep again. He eventually lost his eyes", "actual": ", he was awakened by a friend who brought a holy scripture to his notice, an ancient Pali work.\"\n\n\"Anuruddha is said to have attained nirvana in Bodh-Gaya. It was, in fact, in Bodhgaya that he first met the Buddha who granted him the supreme enlightenment of which he had never before dreamed.\n\n\"By taking his robe, the venerable Anuruddha was the first to give Buddha the veil of the universe.\n\n\"The Buddha, on seeing Anuruddha, said to him: ‘You are a great follower"}
{"prompt": "'use strict';\n\nexports.bdd = require('./bdd');\nexports.tdd", "expected": " = require('./tdd');\nexports.qunit = require('./qunit');\nexports", "actual": " = require('./tdd');\nexports.serve = require('./serve');\nexports.cucumber = require('./cucumber');\nexports.gherkin = require('./gherkin');\nexports.bdd_test = require('./bdd_test');\nexports.cucumber_test = require('./cucumber_test');\nexports.gherkin_test = require('./gherkin_test');\nexports.bdd_xunit = require('."}
{"prompt": "The Mermaids Singing\n\nThe Mermaids Singing (1995) is a crime novel by Scottish author Val McDerm", "expected": "id. The first featuring her recurring protagonist, Dr. Tony Hill, it was adapted into the pilot episode of ITV1's", "actual": "id.\n\nPlot introduction\n\nThe novel takes place in the Scottish village of Morarich, where the young man Jamie MacRae (Jamie) has just arrived to attend the local school, which is now in the process of being taken over by new management. In this new administration the focus is on an area of the new science department, the \"Mermaids Singing\", where a number of women work in close proximity with one another, their lives closely interwoven. On the surface, the mermaids and the school appear to be little more than a social club for the girls – a"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nItemsPanelTemplate issue\n\nI need to use a Grid as PanelTemplate. That's not big deal", "expected": ", but i need to have other controls in that Grid too. So my ItemsControl looks like this:\n<ItemsControl", "actual": " since I already know Grid has a PanelTemplate property.\nHowever: I can't see how to select items (elements) in it. I want to create a Button, a Label, some Textbox etc. The idea is of course to put them all into a Grid.\nI can't understand that the ItemsPanelTemplate property doesn't work with the Grid.\nSo is there any way to put them in a Grid?\nI have a button inside a grid, but I can't select the button.\nThe code is as follows:\n<Grid x:Name=\"LayoutRoot\" Background=\"Trans"}
{"prompt": "// Copyright © 2006-2010 Travis Robinson. All rights reserved.\r\n// \r\n// website: http://source", "expected": "forge.net/projects/libusbdotnet\r\n// e-mail:  libusbdotnet@", "actual": "forge.net/projects/libusbdotnet\r\n// e-mail:  libusbdotnet@gmail.com\r\n// \r\n// This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it\r\n// under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the\r\n// Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or \r\n// (at your option) any later version.\r\n// \r\n// This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but \r\n// WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY;"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nandroid:elevation only have shadow effects on the bottom side, how to make the shadow effects show", "expected": " on top side?\n\nI use a framelayout at the bottom of an activity, in order to show the", "actual": " on the top and bottom?\n\nI made a bottom bar with android:elevation. It has shadow effects on the top and the bottom. That's OK, but I just wanted it to show on the top and bottom.\nThe shadow effects doesn't appear on the top and the bottom. But I need to add some color to those shadow effects, so I made a transparent background for some view on the top and bottom.\nThis is the result:\n\nThis is the XML code that I used:\n<?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"utf-8\"?>\n<menu"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nIs it possible to enable an Org Streaming API through Apex?\n\nIt really is a simple question", "expected": ", just wasn't able to find such information, and the wide availability of streaming apis across the web doesn't help searching", "actual": " that I cannot find a direct answer for.\nI would like to stream an Org, so that I can use the Apex REST or SOAP API, which is available from the Org Explorer in Apex (as described here).\nMy aim is to find out if there is a way to use the Org Streaming API in Apex.  \n\nA:\n\nAfter some experimentation it turns out that the Org Streaming API can be used in Apex only if it is enabled through an Org configuration option, not through a trigger or function.\nIn short:\n\nIn order to use the Or"}
{"prompt": "GEORGE TOWN: Penang Chief Minister Lim Guan Eng is being questioned by police over the \"ABCD-GST", "expected": "\" song, which allegedly criticised the Goods and Services Tax.\n\nLim's statement is being recorded at his office in Kom", "actual": "\" scandal, which involves several prominent Penangites allegedly selling state land at below market price for a profit of up to RM500 million.\n\nThe police have received information that a number of top officials in the Penang government - including the Chief Minister's Chief Secretary, the chief justice, the chief assistant commissioner of police and the Director-General of Public Utilities - are involved in the alleged land deals.\n\nLim, 61, who is also the chairman of the governing People's Action Party (PAP), has been summoned by the police to appear at a designated location on Nov 12 and 13.\n\nChief"}
{"prompt": "Monthly Archives: August 2011\n\nAfter Prophet Muhammad sallallahu alaihi wasalam has finished reciting Sur", "expected": "ah Al Fatihah, he would recite another surah, which he would sometimes prolong and sometimes shorten, because of traveling", "actual": "ah al Furqan he said “O you who have believed! do not be like those unbelievers who are not among the believers!” It then reads “When the believing men or believing women say: ‘Our Lord! accept from us the (belief) which is correct’ and you say ‘No! I do not accept that’ then indeed, God is full of knowledge, He knows the most (correct) of things, and it is no choice for God”. And God is the absolute truth. (Surah Ayyubi Chapter 44: 2-8"}
{"prompt": "No ha pasado una semana desde que Susana Díaz nombró su primer gobierno.", "expected": " Ya anticipó Libertad Digital que el nombramiento de la rectora de la Universidad de M", "actual": " La ex presidenta está en la cima de la crisis en los últimos días. Hace cinco días, la oposición apoyó una exigencia del PPD y de UPyD en el Congreso del país para que algunos de los funcionarios contrarios a la presidenta se hayan reunido con la oposición en las oficinas de una de las formaciones para concluir el diálogo. Una acción común de la opos"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nCombining two table with sql JOIN?\n\nPossible Duplicate:\nCombining several database", "expected": " table together? \n\nI want from two database table get output like this:\n\nOne-week tour of Istanbul", "actual": " tables into one \n\nI'm trying to join two tables and then put them into something that looks like this (id's removed)\nid | event_tid | event_class       | date | time\n  1 |     NULL |              1 |   1|   1\n  2 |     NULL |              1 |   2|   2\n  3 |     NULL |  "}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThe present invention relates to a magnification observation device.\n2. Description of Related Art\n", "expected": "Conventionally, there has been used a magnification observation device, provided with a microscope, for observing an observation object. The", "actual": "In general, an optical microscope has a device for magnifying and observing an object to be observed, and as the device for magnifying and observing the object to be observed, there are a manual type microscope, a so-called automatic type microscope, and the like. In the manual type microscope of this type, the operator observes an object to be observed by an optical system and manually adjusts a focus of the optical system (refer to, for example, Japanese Patent Application Laid-Open No. 2000-222051). Such a manual type microscope has an advantage that the operator himself can easily adjust the focus of"}
{"prompt": "Shopping Cart\n\nMy Account\n\n{\"id\":749320765505,\"title\":\"Kiln Ceramic", "expected": " 4x8 Tile | 103 Colors\",\"handle\":\"kiln-ceramic-tile-4x8\",\"description\":\"\\", "actual": " Tile Set\",\"handle\":\"kiln-ceramic-tile-set\",\"description\":\"\\u003cp\\u003eKiln tiles are a natural stone with the added benefits of being natural and being sustainable. So whether you are planting a garden or just wanting a feature to feature your home, Kiln is the way to go.\\u003c\\/p\\u003e\\n\\u003cp\\u003e\\u003cstrong\\u003eGet your project started today. Order directly from Kiln Ceramics.com.\\u003c\\/strong\\u003e"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nPowershell function to drop table(s) from SQL Server database\n\n### List of tables that", "expected": " require full sanitizing\n$requiredTables = 'table1','table2','table3'\n\nforeach", "actual": " need to be dropped\n$tables = @(\n    # this list just contains the list of tables to be dropped\n    'dbo.Temp_Customer'              ,\n    'dbo.Temp_Customer_Address'      ,\n    'dbo.Temp_Customer_Email'        ,\n    'dbo.Temp_Customer_Phone'        ,\n    'dbo."}
{"prompt": "// ----------------------------------------------------------------------- //\n//\n// MODULE  : SparksFX.cpp\n//\n// PURPOSE : Sparks special FX", "expected": " - Implementation\n//\n// CREATED : 1/17/98\n//\n// ----------------------------------------------------------------------- //\n\n#include", "actual": " system for FX 2.0 and above\n//\n// CREATED : 6/21/99\n//\n// ----------------------------------------------------------------------- //\n\n#include \"SparksFX.h\"\n#include \"SparksObjects.h\"\n#include \"SparksAnimUtil.h\"\n#include \"SparksFXManager.h\"\n#include \"SparksAnimMgr.h\"\n\n#include \"SP_SoundManager.h\"\n\n#include <cstring>\n#include <sstream>\n#include <assert.h>\n"}
{"prompt": "Acetes\n\nAcetes is a genus of small shrimp that resemble krill, which is native to the western", "expected": " and central Indo-Pacific, the Atlantic coast of the Americas, Pacific coast of South America and inland waters of South America.", "actual": " and central Indo-Pacific and parts of the eastern Pacific and Atlantic coasts of Africa. The closest relative is the ctenophore Karyomantis pachyderma, and the two are now considered conspecific. The species usually found in shallow waters (1.2–2.8 m), but have been reported to reach up to 1.5 m in the Bahamas and to 1.7 m in the west coast of Africa. They prefer shallow, oxygen-poor waters with a high-salt concentration, and a high temperature and a high concentration of carbon dioxide. Their small mouth is adapted to extract"}
{"prompt": "Pecan pie would be great - I have tried but do not do that very well, but I \nlove it", "expected": ".  I will probably make pumpkin chiffon and lemon/raspberry pie, so \npecan would be a", "actual": ". What are some of your favorite sweet treats?\n\n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n> \n\n_________________________________________________________________\nGet your FREE download of MSN Explorer at http://explorer.msn.com"}
{"prompt": "When something is illegal, or socially unacceptable, it is forced to lurk in the shadows. The centuries-old sex industry", "expected": " is no exception, and it’s time to allow it to happen above board, in the light of day. When", "actual": " in China has come a long way on this, with the sex workers' rights movement that swept through China in the 1980s, but the same forces — from government to social pressure — that make prostitutes invisible have also helped fuel the growth of the sex industry.\n\nAfter the Second World War, the British government came to realize the importance of sex as a form of currency. In 1919, the government asked an expert in prostitution and a sexologist to assess the problem in Britain. The sexologist, Dr. Ernest Jones, found that as prostitution grew, more and more women were being forced from jobs as prostitutes by the"}
{"prompt": "Cheka, there can never be enough sunken, antediluvian, slime-covered, festering, swamp", "expected": "-swallowed, bizarre, non-euclidean, lizard-man cities, which have stayed hidden, half-", "actual": "y, disease-riddled, ancient swamps. The place where the once-mighty must have their way and no one is allowed to stand in their way, not even the least bit of progress. The place where the world goes to die.\n\nThe only place the world can be saved? It's called the United States of America.\n\nIn case you haven't guessed yet, this post is dedicated to two books—J. K. Potter's The Lost World of Lemuria series, which includes The Lost World of Lemuria, The Lost World of Lemuria II, and The Lost World of"}
{"prompt": "1935 West Virginia Mountaineers football team\n\nThe 1935 West Virginia Mountaineers football team was an American football that", "expected": " represented West Virginia University as an independent during the 1935 college football season. In its second season under head coach Charles Tallman,", "actual": " represented West Virginia University as an independent during the 1935 college football season. In its ninth and final season under the jurisdiction of the University of Virginia, the team compiled a 7–1 record, outscored opponents by a combined total of 213 to 35, scored a total of 1,858 points, and finished the season ranked third in the nation by both Associated Press (AP) and United Press (UP) football writers. The Mountaineers outscored their opponents by a combined total of 214 to 25 in the three seasons that followed.\n\nThe 1935 team was selected by John Heisman as West Virginia's most"}
{"prompt": "Experimental protein and energy deficiencies: effects on brain free amino acid composition in rats.\n1. The effects of protein-", "expected": "energy malnutrition on brain free amino acids of acidic and neutral groups were investigated in experimental rats. 2. Severe energy restriction did", "actual": "energy and energy-protein deficiencies induced in rats by diets that provided the usual dietary protein content but low levels of energy (low-protein diet [LPD]) on brain free amino acid compositions were studied. 2. LPD diets were compared with a usual protein diet (UPD) which provided the usual amount of energy. 3. In both groups, brain free amino acid concentrations were very low except for those of tryptophan and valine in the cerebellum, which were relatively high; this was in agreement with published data of rats fed a normal pelleted diet. 4. In rats fed an L"}
{"prompt": "\"In the city of Mahatma Gandhi and non-violence, how can anyone celebrate a person like Hitler who is known", "expected": " to have murdered millions of unarmed ordinary civilians?\" said Friends of Israel member Nikitin Contractor.\n\nBut co-", "actual": " to be on a rampage against the world and the world will not celebrate him.\" \"But in the city of Mahatma Gandhi and peace, every time there is a war between India and Pakistan, it is known that non-violence is something which can easily defeat violence.\" \"Mahatma Gandhi has said that in a war against terror, non-violence is the only way to beat terrorism which is non-violent.\" \"A leader should think first of his own well-being before he thinks of his followers.\" \"He should sacrifice to his country before he sacrifices to himself.\" \"He should give up all his ambitions"}
{"prompt": "The U.S. is moving to blacklist several Chinese firms behind facial recognition technology that officials say Beijing is using against China�", "expected": "�s Muslim minorities.\n\nThe Commerce Department on Monday applied to put the firms on its Entity List of companies that act", "actual": "s ethnic Uighur minority, the first such move against the country.\n\nThe White House said on Saturday that it would direct officials to begin an immediate review of the technology developed by Beijing�s government-sponsored facial recognition company, the Baidu Inc. group, and any other firms it contracts.\n\nOfficials also said they will begin a review of any applications China might submit to the Federal Communications Commission to allow or prohibit the use of the technology in the United States, in a move they said was designed to protect people�s privacy.\n\nThe move comes after the U.S. government black"}
{"prompt": "4962 Vecherka\n\n4962 Vecherka, provisional designation, is a Eunomian asteroid and slow", "expected": " rotator from the central regions of the asteroid belt, approximately 10 kilometers in diameter. It was discovered on 1 October 1973,", "actual": " rotator from the outer belt, approximately  in diameter. It was discovered on 24 December 1969, by British astronomer Brian Warner at Oakley Observatory in California. The asteroid was named for Russian astronomer Viktor Vecherka (1896–1952).\n\nClassification and orbit \n\nVecherka is a member of the Eunomia family (), a dynamical group of nearly 400 known asteroid and near-Earth objects (NEOs) with small orbits and very low eccentricity. Its leading side and rotation period of about 8.26 hours have been determined independently from observations at two American radio observ"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nHow to use max() function to retrieve the most recent row using SQL / postgreSQL\n\nI have", "expected": " a data set that looks like this \nexample data set.\nThere are multiple users under one domain. I want only", "actual": " a table of orders and want to be able to select the most recent order by orderid. If the id is higher than some value then I will return it. If it is not then I'll return the older one. If the orderid is equal to the id I'm interested in then I want the older one. \nI'm a beginner in SQL and I have a problem with the most recent row. I'm not sure how to use the max() function to retrieve the most recent row.\nHere is some sample data. The goal is to be able to retrieve the date when the most recent order was"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nI want to render the number of images and images should be shuffle in react native? how to do that", "expected": "? Can any one help me\n\nImages should be shuffle when i'll click on that particular image in react native.\n", "actual": " in react native\n\nI want to render the number of images and images should be shuffled in react native? How to do that in react native ?\nhere is the code in home.js : \nimport React, {Component} from 'react';\nimport {\n  View,\n  Text,\n  StyleSheet,\n  TouchableOpacity,\n  Image,\n  Dimensions\n} from 'react-native';  \nimport {Button} from 'react-native-elements';\n\nexport default class Home extends Component {\n  constructor(props) {"}
{"prompt": "<?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"UTF-8\"?>\n<!-- \n/*\n* Copyright (", "expected": "C) 2017 The Android Open Source Project\n*\n* Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"", "actual": "C) 2017 The Android Open Source Project\n*\n* Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");\n* you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n* You may obtain a copy of the License at\n*\n*      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n*\n* Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n* distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,\n* WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY K"}
{"prompt": "This App Will Notify You If Trump Tweets About A Company You’re Invested In\n\nTrump’", "expected": "s tweets are proving again and again to have the capacity to make significant waves.\n\nNow there’s an app", "actual": "s attack on Nordstrom on Twitter last night was in response to a story on the company that claimed a customer complained that Trump “shops Nordstrom for his daughter’s wedding.”\n\nNordstrom released a statement Friday night, but on Saturday afternoon they went silent.\n\n“Nordstrom takes the concerns of customers very seriously, and is currently investigating. Until we know more, we will continue to keep our customers informed and take any appropriate measures.”\n\nAnd while we’re waiting for Nordstrom to release more information, here’s something that we"}
{"prompt": "[Hypothesis for a pre- and post-natal relationship between mother and child].\nThe increasing interest in prenatal life", "expected": " triggered this study of the hypothetical possibilities of communication between mother and foetus. In this context, sound in the general sense is", "actual": "-history studies has led to increasingly complex models of the development of the human child. In our study, we apply an approach that focuses on the prenatal, intrapartum and neonatal period using a theoretical perspective that integrates both evolutionary and ecological systems and considers the effects of intrauterine processes on the individual and the phenotype of the offspring. In our view, the main biological mechanisms that influence the development of the individual during intrauterine life are the effects of the maternal phenotype: the intrauterine environment and the intrauterine immune system. We conclude that there is no direct correlation between the intrauterine physiology and"}
{"prompt": "In video footage the transit agency released Tuesday, the victim can be seen sitting on a bench near the southbound side of the", "expected": " tracks shortly before 2 a.m., when he slumps forward and falls to the floor of the platform.", "actual": " Green Line tracks.\n\nAuthorities haven’t said whether the man was injured, and a spokesman for the transit agency said investigators were still gathering facts. There’s no indication of how the boy got in the tracks, and police haven’t said how they would proceed if the man is found to have accidentally gotten on the tracks.\n\nThe incident comes four months after a child died in a Green Line train when he allegedly fell off of one tracks on the same line where the boy died.\n\nThis latest incident has occurred on the same Green Line track where two women were killed after allegedly falling"}
{"prompt": "Index Labels\n\nDOCTOR WHO: Roman Arc - The Fires Of Pompeii\n\nWe round the \"R", "expected": "ome Arc\" off nicely now with the Tenth Doctor's timely stopover in Pompeii, which would later mark the start of", "actual": "\" at Pompeii (the Roman city that is famous for its destruction in 79 A.D.) by looking at Roman Architecture.\n\nWhen people think of ancient Rome, there are two things they immediately think of: The Colosseum, the Roman Colosseum, which still stands today, and the city that would come to be known as the city of Pompeii, and which was destroyed by a mysterious eruption of Mount Vesuvius about 80 years before this series was filmed (in 79 C.E.)\n\nThe Romans' most important achievements in architecture were at the Circus Maximus, the Forum"}
{"prompt": "Less than two weeks after operatives of the Tin-Can Island Command of the Nigeria Customs Service, NCS, busted a synd", "expected": "icate that smuggled over 1,000 weapons into Nigeria, another container containing guns has been apprehended.\n\nThe container was shipped", "actual": "icate behind the world’s biggest counterfeit of cell phones, in which a huge number of Nigerians were victims, they were forced to take down the website and cell phone number of the syndicate’s leader.\n\nThe police operatives claimed that the leader and three others used the website, http://www.cinema.africa.ng/index.html, to distribute counterfeit cell phones over the internet.\n\nOn Monday, 25th February, 2009 at about 12.30am, Police in Lagos, NCS operatives laid a trap at Koye, Ota, Oj"}
{"prompt": "package org.enso.languageserver.capability\n\nimport org.enso.languageserver.data", "expected": ".CapabilityRegistration\nimport org.enso.languageserver.filemanager.FileSystemFailure\nimport org.", "actual": ".{Environment, EnvironmentData, EnvironmentType}\n\n/**\n  * A class for managing capabilities.\n  *\n  * Each environment can have up to four capabilities (for example\n  * the Env.Capabilities of EnvironmentData.Maven, for a project for which the\n  * MavenRepository trait has been implemented).\n  *\n  * This class represents the capabilities available in an environment. It\n  * contains a list of environment capabilities and environment\n  * dependencies.\n  *\n  * See [[Environment]] for a description of the structure of environment\n"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nI am having a IndexError: list index out of range error trying to grab the text from an xml", "expected": " file\n\nI am having an error when trying to iterate through the metadata tags from my xml file and grabbing the text", "actual": " tag\n\nI am getting errors when trying to use the below code. I have tried other solutions but I am not getting the desired results.\nfrom xml.etree import ElementTree\n\ntree = ElementTree.fromstring('D:\\\\Sites\\\\Test\\\\Test.xml')\n\ntest = tree.find('//test')\ntest.text\n\nThis is the xml file\n\n    <?xml version=\"1.0\"?>\n    <test>\n        <name>Test</name>\n      "}
{"prompt": "Habitat for Humanity: The sign-up sheet for CLC to volunteer at a Habitat for Humanity Build this coming", "expected": " Sat., Sept. 23 is in the hallway. Please consider joining us. NO EXPERIENCE is needed. Volunteers will meet", "actual": " May is now available. It is a short but sweet description of three benefits of volunteering in Habitat for Humanity's \"Home for the Homeless\" program: \"You'll have a chance to help build homes for families in need. You'll have a chance to learn more about the program and the work that they do in your community. You'll have a chance to play a role in an important part of your community's history and future. \"C-list celebrities and other people of power will sign the sheet for you. This is a way to showcase the skills you have and the abilities you have to contribute to a cause"}
{"prompt": "A smoking mountain near the Yukon River not far from Eagle is, after further study, still a puzzle.\n\nPeople", "expected": " first noticed acrid smoke in September 2012. The mountain has been steaming ever since, even during the coldest days of", "actual": " have long been attracted to the nearby valley of Cripple Creek, where the main part of the story of the discovery of gold lies. But just who made the first gold discovery in this part of the Yukon remains a mystery. One reason is that there are no written records of this find. There are only oral histories of the time—perhaps as many as 30 different stories of how the gold was discovered.\n\nA second reason why the first gold discovery may have happened here is that this part of the gold rush trail between the Yukon and northern British Columbia was cut off for most of the 1850s, and"}
{"prompt": "\n625 So.2d 815 (1993)\nRonald G. HUBBARD\nv.\nSTATE", "expected": " of Alabama ex rel. Heddy E. HUBBARD.\nAV92000174.\nCourt of Civil", "actual": " of Mississippi.\nNo. 91-CA-01516 COA.\nCourt of Appeals of Mississippi.\nJune 18, 1993.\n*816 Ronald G. Hubbard, appellant, pro se.\nOffice of the Attorney General by Sarah B. Gibboney, Sp. Asst. Atty. Gen., Jackson, for appellees.\nBefore HAWKINS, P.J., and PRATHER and ROBERTSON, JJ.\nPRATHER, Judge, for the Court:\nThis is an appeal by Ronald G. Hubbard from a Circuit Court of Jackson County's dismissal of"}
{"prompt": "(1) Field of the Invention\nThe present invention relates generally to radio frequency (RF) linear power amplifier bias networks and", "expected": ", more particularly, to a bias network for minimizing distortion products normally associated with bipolar transistor based RF power amplifiers.\n(", "actual": " to linearized bias controllers for such amplifiers.\n(2) Description of the Related Art\nA radio frequency power amplifier is used in mobile communications to amplify and transmit analog or digital signals over the allocated channel bandwidth, and it therefore presents the additional problem in many applications that it should have adequate linearity (gain) and linearity (power) over a wide input dynamic range. A widely used linearity enhancement technique is to use a bias circuit which comprises a linear amplifier in combination with a bias network. The linear amplifier is typically a power amplifier and is fed with negative feedback. A linearizer is normally provided at a"}
{"prompt": "Analysis of tyrosine- and methionine-containing neuropeptides by fast atom bombardment mass spectrometry.", "expected": "\nA simple and unambiguous method for the detection of the amino acids tyrosine and methionine in peptide structures", "actual": "\nThe cationic peptidase N. cuniculi was investigated for its capacity to cleave the carboxyl-terminal peptide Y(2)Y(2) from neuropeptides, including cholecystokinin-28 (CCK-28). The cleavage products were investigated by negative-ion fast atom bombardment mass spectrometry following post-source decay (PSD) fragmentation. In the case of CCK-28, all peptide cleavage sites were located, confirming its proteolytic origin. The molecular mass of the intact CCK-28 was increased by"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nDoes $\\int_{0}^{\\infty}{\\sin{(\\pi{x^2})", "expected": "}\\over \\sinh{(\\pi{x}})\\tanh(x\\pi)}\\mathrm{d}", "actual": "}}dx=-\\frac{\\pi^3}{6}$?\n\nProve that \n$$\\int_{0}^{\\infty}{\\sin{(\\pi{x^2})}}dx=-\\frac{\\pi^3}{6}$$\n\nI tried to use the property of the complex exponential:\n$$e^{ix}=e^{ix}\\cdot e^{i(x+ix)}=-ie^{ix}(e^{ix}+e^{-ix})$$\nI used this in the following integral:\n$$\\int_{0}^{\\in"}
{"prompt": "The number of elderly people caught shoplifting in Japan's capital city has outstripped that of teenagers for the first time since", "expected": " records began, a report said.\n\nA quarter of the people arrested on suspicion of the crime in Tokyo last year were", "actual": " records began in the early 2000s.\n\nTokyo Metropolitan Police reported a 17 per cent increase in shoplifting incidents for the past nine months.\n\nShoplifters are stealing items ranging from food to handbags. Many elderly people steal from home, so shoplifting is a growing problem in Japan. ( AFP: Toushin Kitaoka)\n\nOn a Thursday, police estimated that the elderly were stealing $5.8 million worth of goods in the past year.\n\nThis came after similar figures reported in the years leading up to last year.\n\n\"We are facing a new and serious"}
{"prompt": "define: DUK_USE_BUFFEROBJECT_SUPPORT\nintroduced: 1.3.0\ndefault", "expected": ": true\ntags:\n  - ecmascript2015\ndescription: >\n  Enable support for Khronos/", "actual": ": NULL\n\nSee also:\n    duk_get_bufferobj_hook,  duk_get_bufferobj_data\ndescription:\n    This function can be used to store a pointer to the buffer object used by the\n    current state.  Use this if you need to store a pointer to the current state\n    directly.\n\n    The pointer passed to the hook function can be either a global object, or a\n    fixed buffer object in which case the size is always the same.\nReturns:\n   "}
{"prompt": "Max González Olaechea\n\nMaximiliano González Olaechea (November 30, 18", "expected": "67 in Arequipa, Peru – February 5, 1946 in Ica) was a Peruvian doctor, clinician", "actual": "53 – December 20, 1932) was a Cuban politician, journalist and journalist. He was the Prime Minister, a member of the Chamber of Deputies of the second Cuban republic, and the President of the Senate of Cuba from 1900 to 1912.\n\nBiography\n\nEarly years\nOlaechea was born on November thirty-first, 1853 in the small island village of Coto. His father was a criollo mambí-criollo sugar cultivator and he moved to Havana, at the age of six, to work with his uncle, a planter. At eight, Maximil"}
{"prompt": "~ Novelist\n\nAuthor Archives: JMcNChicago\n\nSummers on the Nebraska Shore explores the dynamics and fluid", "expected": " nature of family. Love, passion and loss feature prominently. Edwin Garside, a successful novelist, reviews his nomadic", "actual": "ity of this diverse region of the Midwest. It examines the history and cultures of each of 14 states along the North Platte River. These states have played a pivotal part in the area’s development as a trade and transportation hub.\n\nThe author, a native of the Omaha area, presents the history and cultures of each region’s communities, as well the political and economic issues that have shaped them. The chapters contain historic and cultural photographs, drawings, maps, maps, and oral histories from each community.\n\nAuthor JMcNChicago will be in the Omaha area, at the Missouri Writers�"}
{"prompt": "Introduction\n============\n\nVarious placental and cord abnormalities have been known to adversely affect the obstetric outcome. Circumv", "expected": "allate placenta is an abnormality of the placental shape where there is a central depression on the foetal", "actual": "allate placenta (CVP), the most common placenta anomaly worldwide, is associated with increased pregnancy loss and perinatal morbidity. The CVP is characterized by the fusion of the umbilical cord into the placental villi and is usually diagnosed in the third trimester. The reported frequency of CVP varies by country and depends on the diagnostic criteria and selection of patients. Most CVP cases are detected by placental MRI scans at the time of delivery, while some cases are found at the time of cesarean section (CS) due to the suspicion of fetal malpresentation.["}
{"prompt": "BRANDING, PHOTOGRAPHY + ART. Europe, Australia, America.\n\nBranding design: Build", "expected": " from the Heart- out.\n\nThis collection is a celebration of simplicity. To build a strong brand you must begin from", "actual": "s relationships with the public on the level of trust. It is a form of public relations that has a measurable and positive effect on branding's customer's brand awareness, loyalty, and purchase intent.\n\nHow to implement: The branding approach is divided in three phases:\n\n- Designing a great brand for your business (e.g. a logo, a website, a marketing slogan, etc.)- Developing a brand personality- Building a strong brand through the power of the brand personality (e.g. a logo, a name, a tagline, etc.)\n\nThe branding design process involves several"}
{"prompt": "\n850 P.2d 642 (1993)\nBruce COLE (deceased) and Lorena Cole (", "expected": "widow), Appellants,\nv.\nKETCHIKAN PULP COMPANY and Alaska Timber Insurance", "actual": "deceased), individually and all other heirs of the Estate of Bruce Cole, Deceased, Plaintiffs,\nv.\nTURNER COUNTY SCHOOL DISTRICT, a political subdivision and school district; and T. Alan Taylor, as Sheriff of Turner County, Defendants, and\nRobert F. Hulme, M.D., Defendant-Appellant,\nIn the Matter of BRUCE COLES, Deceased, and Mary Ellen Cole, as personal representative of the Estate of Bruce Cole; and Douglas Cole, as guardian of Bruce Cole and Lorena Cole, Plaintiffs-Appellees."}
{"prompt": "// @flow\n\ndeclare module 'glob' {\n  declare type GlobFn = {\n  ", "expected": "  (\n      sources: string,\n      callback: (err: null |", "actual": "  (\n      path: string,\n      cwd?: string,\n      options?: Object,\n      callback: Function\n    ) => any\n  }\n  declare type GlobPath = any // https://github.com/nodejs/node/pull/37892\n\n  declare type NpmFn = {\n    (\n      path: string,\n      cwd?: string,\n      options?: Object,\n "}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nBuild NuGet package for multiple framework targets from Visual Studio 2010 project file\n\nInternally within my organisation", "expected": " we maintain a code library, some of our applications are built on.NET 4 while older applications are still built on.NET", "actual": ", Visual Studio 2010 uses an assembly file to build out the NuGet package for a specific set of .NET Framework 4.6 targets.\nThe target is specified in the build-targets.json file.\n{  \n   \"targets\": [\n        {\n            \"target\"  : \"Foo\",\n            \"type\"    : \"Framework\",\n            \"configurations"}
{"prompt": "{{# def.definitions }}\n{{# def.errors }}\n{{# def.setupKeyword }}\n{{", "expected": "# def.$data }}\n\n{{ var $op = $keyword =='maxLength'? '>' :", "actual": "# def.$data }}\n\n{{\n  var $rule = this\n    , $definition = 'definition' + $lvl\n    , $rlang = 'rlang' + $lvl\n    , $dataNodes = 'data-node' + $lvl\n    , $XPATH = ' XPATH ' + $lvl\n    , $braces = '{}[]()'\n    , $relate = 'relate' + $lvl\n    , $unpack = 'unpack' + $"}
{"prompt": "Gwersyllt\n\nGwersyllt () is an urban village and a local government community, the lowest", "expected": " tier of local government, part of Wrexham County Borough in Wales.\n\nThe densely populated village is one of W", "actual": " tier in Wales, in the community of Gower. Situated on the south coast of the Vale of Glamorgan, just north of Abergavenny, it is at the end of Gwersyllt Bay.\n\nGwersyllt is noted as a centre of the Welsh language movement at the centre of Wales in the 19th century, and it was an early home of Welsh Nationalism. Today it is the centre of the Abergavenny-based Welsh Language Society and the principal settlement of the Gwersyllt Local Board in the Vale of Glamorgan.\n\nHistory\nG"}
{"prompt": "#!/usr/bin/env bash\n\nflutter format.\nflutter packages pub publish --dry-run\n", "expected": "flutter packages pub publish -v", "actual": "\necho \"flutter packages pub pub version=\"$(flutter packages pub publish --local > /dev/null \\\n  | sed -r 's/flutter/local/; s/pub/pub/' -e 's/\\(//g') \\\n  | sed -r 's/\\(\\.\\)\\(//g')\n\nreadonly version=$(git rev-parse HEAD)\n\necho \"flutter package flutter_webview version=\"$version\"\n\nflutter_webview=$(echo \"flutter_webview=$version\""}
{"prompt": "[Oxidative stress in victims with heavy combined cranium-facial trauma].\nFor acute posttraumatic period of heavy", "expected": " combined cranium-facial trauma (CFT) considerable activation of peroxide lipids oxidation in the liquor is typical beginning", "actual": " combined cranium-facial trauma, the severity of oxidative damage in the blood was measured in 15 patients and the results were compared with the results of a control group of 15 healthy volunteers. The following parameters were investigated: blood lipid peroxide content, red blood cell lipid peroxide content, activity of antioxidant enzymes: glutathione red blood cell-reduced glutathione, superoxide disulphide dismutase, catalase, and glutathione S-transferase. Blood glutathione red blood cell redox potential and glutathione S-transferase activity were also measured. Patients with combined"}
{"prompt": "Oscars: 'World War Z' is among the 289 films eligible for 'Best Picture'\n\nBy Iain", "expected": " Alexander / 17 December 2013\n\nWorld War Z poster 2013\n\nAcademy announces eligible films\n\nThe 2013 selection", "actual": " Lynn\n\n14 January 2015\n\nLast week saw the release of the 83rd Academy Awards, where the selection of the nominees saw a record number of films from five countries, with more than 30 new titles up for recognition.\n\nThe best picture category saw a record-breaking number of entries, with 84, including 16 in the animated category, and the likes of “Mad Max: Fury Road” and “The Wolf of Wall Street” making the nominations shortlist.\n\nThe long list of nominations featured a wide range of movies, with the likes of “The Tree of Life�"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nSwipeRefreshLayout setRefreshing not showing progress bar in Fragment\n\nI am using", "expected": " the following code in this fragment:\npublic class OwnerPendingBookingsFragment extends Fragment implements SwipeRefresh", "actual": " the following code to implement a swipe-refresh-like Activity.\nBut there seems to be something wrong with the \nsetRefreshing(true) \n\nmethod. When I click on a button, the swiprefresh is showing like it should, but the progress bar is not showing. Can anyone show me what I am doing wrong? Thanks\nHere is my layout file:\n<?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"utf-8\"?>\n<android.support.v4.widget.SwipeRefreshLayout xmlns:android=\"http://schemas."}
{"prompt": "University of Windsor business professor Alfie Morgan could hardly be labeled a disciple of the left-leaning Kathleen Wynne regime but he believes", "expected": " the premier is on the side of the angels in fast-tracking a $15 minimum wage.\n\nI happen to think", "actual": " he can win the Liberal endorsement under the current circumstances.\n\n“I am going to try,” Morgan told the Star when speaking to reporters in a conference call on Wednesday.\n\n“When I got appointed, I thought I had been appointed to a position of leadership. I’ve now been told that it’s a political role of being a lackey and working around the cabinet. And I have to go out there and find a support group,” he explained.\n\nMorgan is one of several left-leaning professors and researchers who have come to see the Wynne government as"}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThe present invention relates to a source driver, and more particularly, to a source driver with", "expected": " high driving ability, high stability and high charge-sharing efficiency.\n2. Description of the Prior Art\nPlease refer to", "actual": " an improved timing margin by using a differential circuit of a complementary PNP transistor.\n2. Description of the Background Art\nIn general, a source driver is needed to drive a liquid crystal panel. The source driver includes a first switch section for driving a first pair of the data lines (D.sub.1 and D.sub.2) and a second switch section for driving a second pair of the data lines (D.sub.3 and D.sub.4). The first pair of the data lines is connected to the liquid crystal panel and to the first switch section through a first common line, which is"}
{"prompt": "IgH gene rearrangements on the unexpressed allele in rabbit B cells.\nVDJ genes are assembled in two", "expected": " sequential DNA recombination steps, rearrangement of D and J(H) gene segments followed by rearrangement of a", "actual": " ways in rabbit B cells: (a) by homologous joining between V, D, and J segments, or (b) by simultaneous homologous and nonhomologous recombinations. In both cases, each V, D, and J segment is paired with a homologous partner, either a J/I or a J/T segment. We have examined recombination at the IgH locus in spleen cells and bone marrow cells of inbred rabbits using Southern blot analysis. This technique was also used to monitor recombination of IgH segments in B cells cultured from spleen and bone marrow cells"}
{"prompt": "Some conventional Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems have provided statistics or other feedback regarding use of the IVR system, but", "expected": " no one prior to the inventor has created or used the invention described in the appended claims.", "actual": " do not provide information regarding IVR calls that either are not answered because the caller does not have an appointment or the IVR call was made but the caller does not have access to the desired information. Even when a caller uses the system, the information contained in an IVR call often is not useful because the caller must go through several pages to find the information of interest. Therefore, it is desirable to provide methods and systems for providing IVR callers with information regarding the IVR call that was not provided to the caller during the IVR call."}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nTwo functions don't work together, but no errors\n\nI have a couple of javascript functions which:", "expected": "\n\nshow/hide some table rows\nadd a new row\n\nBoth work on the same page, but not under", "actual": "\n\nShow/Hide a <div> depending on whether the user selects checkboxes in a table.\nHide a <h2> (which is only shown if the <div> was displayed).\n\nAs of now, only the first function works. I also want to mention that when I call the first function, the <div> will be hidden, and then after a second function, the <div> will be shown again. When the second function is called the <div> will only be shown after the <div> was hidden.\nThe first function works perfectly, but the second function, or"}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThis invention relates to a back light detecting method, a back light detecting device and an image", "expected": " pick-up camera, in which a back light state is detected according to a subject image.\n2. Description of the", "actual": " forming apparatus.\n2. Description of the Related Art\nConventional image forming apparatuses such as copiers, laser beam printers or facsimile machines have a photosensitive drum, which is exposed to a light beam to form an electrostatic latent image. The electrostatic latent image formed on the photosensitive drum (hereinafter called a photosensitive member) is developed into a toner image and is thereafter transferred onto a paper sheet. Recently, such image forming apparatuses are required to be capable of miniaturization, high speed operations, and further, energy conservation. To meet such requirements, the elect"}
{"prompt": "\n808 A.2d 994 (2002)\nINDUSTRIAL RECISION SERVICES and Ohio Casualty Group,", "expected": " Petitioners,\nv.\nWORKERS' COMPENSATION APPEAL BOARD (FARBO), Respondent", "actual": " Plaintiffs,\nv.\nCOMMONWEALTH INSURANCE COMPANY, Defendant.\nCommonwealth Insurance Company, Third-Party Plaintiff,\nv.\nBarry Johnson and Robert Johnson, Third-Party Defendants.\nSupreme Court of Delaware.\nSubmitted: September 13, 2001.\nDecided: April 2, 2002.\nJoseph W. Vecchione and Michael F. Nesi of Ashby & Geddes, Wilmington, for Industrial Recision Services.\nEdward A. Gerety of Richards, Layton & Finger, Wilmington, for Ohio Casualty Group.\nJeff"}
{"prompt": "Hummingbird Magnet for Glendale Landscaping\n\nThese tiny birds are fascinating and many are eager to attract them to", "expected": " their yard. You’ll need more than red-tinted sugar water in a hummingbird feeder though if", "actual": " feed.\n\nI was thrilled to be able to host a hummingbird family on our last Saturday.\n\nThe sun was warm but not too hot. The hummingbirds seemed to be enjoying the beautiful day.\n\nThere was some activity in the surrounding shrubs and the hummingbirds weren’t deterred by the noise of the family as they came to visit me and my small family.\n\nI was thrilled to hear the song of the male. There’s one species of hummingbird from which the male sings the most beautiful songs.\n\nSome other of the families that visit the hummingbird"}
{"prompt": "/*\n * Copyright (C) 2000 Alfredo Andres Omella.  All rights reserved.\n *\n * Red", "expected": "istribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n * modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions\n", "actual": "istribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without\n * modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions\n * are met:\n *\n *   Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright\n *     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n *\n *   Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright\n *     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in\n *     the documentation and/or other materials provided with the\n *     distribution.\n *"}
{"prompt": "Main menu\n\nYou are here\n\nError message\n\nDeprecated function: The each() function is deprecated. This", "expected": " message will be suppressed on further calls in _menu_load_objects() (line 579 of /home/countrys", "actual": " message will be suppressed on further calls in menu_set_active_traffic().\n\nSubmitted by\n\nThe City of Atlanta plans to reduce traffic and improve pedestrian and bike safety on Atlanta BeltLine and Peachtree Street by constructing an off-street bike and pedestrian path, which is a component of the multi-phase construction, called the BeltLine Improvements Project.\n\nThe BeltLine is a 1.5-mile continuous linear park, which is a component of the BeltLine Parkway. The BeltLine also includes the adjacent Peachtree Street pedestrian and biking corridor and a bike/pedestrian bridge"}
{"prompt": "There are 101 non-fiction, and several fiction, books credited to popular science and mathematics writer Martin Gardner (1914-", "expected": "2010), who would have turned 101 on October 21. Among the myriad math problems that Martin presented in his influential Mathematical", "actual": "1994). He was a prolific inventor and one of the key people in the development of electronic computers and video games.\n\nAfter the completion of their Master’s Thesis at Oxford in 1958, Gombrich and Gardner wrote their thesis research paper on the art of the modern painter (Gombrich & Gardner, 1958).\n\nTheses and Research Papers\n\nIn 1969, they published The Art of the Modern Painter, a compendium of contemporary works, mainly in photography, painting and graphic arts.\n\nGardner’s best-known books include The New Inventors,"}
{"prompt": "Effects of Reactive Oxygen Species on Differentiation of Bone Marrow Mesenchymal Stem Cells.\nBACKGROUND", "expected": " The low differentiation rates for transplanted stem cells are challenging problems in spinal cord injury (SCI) treatment. Studies have demonstrated", "actual": ": In recent years, increasing attention has been paid to the role of reactive oxygen species (ROS) in stem cell differentiation. It was revealed that the number of mitochondria in mitochondria-associated membrane proteins and the level of mitochondrial ROS in differentiating cells were closely related to the process of cell differentiation. Additionally, it was reported that ROS increased the process of osteogenic differentiation of bone marrow mesenchymal stem cells (BMSCs). METHODS: The differentiation of BMSCs into osteoblasts is a typical differentiation process of mesenchymal stem cells. In our study, cell morphology changes,"}
{"prompt": "Bridge Program Advising\n\nAll students interested in our Bridge program must apply for regular admission to AUM. AUM will", "expected": " admit students into our Bridge program based on qualifications.\n\nAll Bridge program students must sign a Bridge Program Contract in order to", "actual": " approve a limited number of applicants who meet this eligibility requirement. Our initial enrollment in the program will be limited to 120 students. It is imperative that you plan to attend our Bridge Program if you are accepted to our admission decision process.\n\nWe understand the importance of making your choice from among all our available AUM programs. Therefore, we only consider applications on a rolling basis. This means that you do not need to apply for admission to AUM every year.\n\nHow to Apply\n\nTo apply for admission to our Bridge Program, follow these steps when you submit your admission application:\n\nSubmit the admission application"}
{"prompt": "This article is the subject of a legal complaint from Sheikh Hamad bin Jassim bin Jaber al-Thani.", "expected": "\n\nA former prime minister of Qatar is attempting to use his UK diplomatic immunity to halt a court case in London where he", "actual": " The information contained in this article is based on the allegations and materials in the complaint.\n\nThis article discusses some of the allegations made in the complaint as follows:\n\n1. The United Kingdom (UK) has been supporting the UAE government and the UAE military alliance against Qatar for years in order to isolate Qatar and control it through the UN Security Council.\n\n2. The UAE and the UAE Armed Forces launched a massive ”humanitarian” operation on June 5, 2017, which resulted in the deaths of numerous civilians who were killed, captured, tortured, raped and were made to commit suicide.\n\n"}
{"prompt": "France women's national rugby union team\n\nThe France women's national rugby union team first played in 1982.\n\nHistory", "expected": "\nSource: \"Des Filles en Ovalie\", Editions Atlantica (2005), Written by Jacques Corte /", "actual": "\nFrance and Scotland share a long-standing tradition with women's rugby in the French Rugby Union, and with Scotland and Wales, in the All-Blacks Wales Rugby Union.\n\nAfter having a team which won the 1991 Eurocup competition, the French Rugby Federation decided to play in the 1995 Women's Rugby World Cup. France was the only representative team from Europe, as the other nations are from the North American and Australasian regions. The team finished fourth in the tournament. France also participated (as an invited team) in the 2002 Women's Rugby World Cup.\n\nIn the 2005 Women's Rugby World"}
{"prompt": "Source IM Defensoras\n\nFACTS – On Sunday, September 8, defender of Garifuna territory Mirna", "expected": " Teresa Suazo Martínez was killed by unidentified persons who arrived by motorcycle at the restaurant she owned in the community of", "actual": " Peña was arrested for entering the US with overstayed student status. Since then she has been facing deportation. In March of this year her court date was set for April, but now she has been taken away for an indefinite period of time by ICE.\n\nOn Friday, Peña, an associate professor in the Department of Anthropology at Florida International University in Miami, was taken into custody. At the same time, Immigration agents from the Immigration & Customs Enforcement agency (ICE) arrived on the university campus and arrested two other faculty who had previously been granted release on bond.\n\nDuring this time an international social justice"}
{"prompt": "The effects of both single-locus and multi-locus interaction on the clinical manifestations of IgA nephropathy", "expected": " in Southern Han Chinese.\nImmunoglobulin A nephropathy (IgAN) is one of the", "actual": " (IgAN) were studied in a case-control study involving 648 patients with IgAN and 5,108 matched controls drawn from the population-based control study. The mean age of the IgAN patients was 32 years, and the mean age of the controls was 33 years. The sex ratio of the IgAN patients was 1.05 (male:female). IgAN was diagnosed by means of the International Society of Nephrology/Renal Pathology Society classification. The most commonly affected organs were the skin and liver. The single-locus linkage analysis of the IgAN cases identified 12 loci that were"}
{"prompt": "This is a competing continuation to support six post-doctoral positions to provide rigorous research training for pulmonary physicians at the fellowship level and", "expected": " Ph.D. recipients with interests in lung disease. The ultimate goal is to develop pulmonary scientists in either basic or clinical research", "actual": " to support five post-doctoral fellows to participate in research with postdoctoral fellows and the development of skills in translational science. This new award will further extend the training opportunities for young pulmonary physicians at the fellowship level, and add an essential component of research training. This award is designed to support young investigators from diverse backgrounds for the next three years. This award will support two postdoctoral fellows from each of the five disciplines, including pulmonary medicine; the two postdoctoral fellows will jointly develop a research project in which this award will provide the funding for one junior faculty member who will participate in this project. It will also fund mentoring"}
{"prompt": "GRDDL\n\nGRDDL (pronounced \"griddle\") is a markup format for Gleaning Resource Descriptions", "expected": " from Dialects of Languages. It is a W3C Recommendation, and enables users to obtain RDF triples", "actual": " (GRDs). It is an extension to the web standard Extensible Markup Language (XML). GRDDL is supported by nearly all open source and proprietary software that generates XML documents. GRDDL is intended to be a universal resource description format for describing information on the Web.\n\nA GRD is made up of a title and resource key (the \"resource name\" in the context of GRDDL), either separated by a semicolon (;) or by a comma (,). The title has a URI value that begins with @.  The GRD definition is composed of a collection of"}
{"prompt": "Thermal Tolerance and Prediction of Northern Distribution of the Crapemyrtle Bark Scale (Hemiptera: E", "expected": "riococcidae).\nPhysiological limits of non-native species to environmental factors are critical for their establishment and spread in", "actual": "riosomatidae).\nHemiparasites have long been known to play major roles in the functioning of ecosystems. We use data on the occurrence of two bark scale species (Crapemyrtle angulata Kieser) in five Canadian provinces, to explore (1) the factors associated with their potential distribution in response to changes in climate, and (2) to predict the northern distribution of C. angulata based on its known distribution in Canada and its potential for range expansion. We predicted that increased temperature is a limiting factor to northern expansion of C. angulata, while precipitation"}
{"prompt": "Comets whizzing beyond our solar system made a big splash last year when astronomers discovered that they could be as common", "expected": " as alien planets. Now, for the first time, researchers have surveyed a large population of these “exocomets", "actual": " as birds and whales in our Milky Way galaxy.\n\nNow they have found a new cosmic contender for the title of the busiest star out there — one so fast it could have been picked up by some sort of interplanetary telescope.\n\nLast year, the European Southern Observatory (ESO) found 685 new comets, or icyballs that are too far away from our sun to have been discovered until now. Now, following up on these results, researchers have used NASA’s Spitzer Space Telescope to discover that another comet, named C/2013 W1, has reached speeds similar to that of"}
{"prompt": "Hamilton–Lay Store\n\nThe Hamilton–Lay Store, also known as the Hamilton Crossroads Store, is a historic country", "expected": " general store at Hamilton Crossroads (the intersection of Mill Pond Hollow Road and Walkers Ford Road) in Union County, Tennessee", "actual": " general store at 714 King Street SW in Chattanooga, Tennessee.  It is listed on the National Register of Historic Places.\n\nLocation and history\nThe store is located at the junction of the north-south King Highway and the east-west Highway 51.  The building is actually on the southwest corner of King and Woodland Roads, with its windows facing King from the highway.  It is a two-story wood frame structure with a gable roof, built in the late 1880s as part of a larger, two-storey building that also served as a drugstore, general store and general office building"}
{"prompt": "Description\nnew hose to fit all dyson dc 27 free uk delivery same day postage free uk postage we dispatch within", "expected": " 24 hours of payment use paypal or to pay using a credit debit card call us 01246 451113 mon fri 9", "actual": " 24 hours order by 12 days we will ship every single day delivery within 2 day is also available for some products to international as long as all shipping documents are in order we do our best to provide you with a hassle free experience with our fast free UK delivery service if you wish to use your credit card on payment you must call before you pay to avoid unnecessary transaction fees\n\nDyson DC27 FreeHose is highly durable and has a unique design, which ensures that it is easy to use and will last for long\nThe free jet nozzle allows the hose to be cleaned easily\nThe hose has a soft grip on the"}
{"prompt": "Samar (province)\n\nSamar, formerly named as Western Samar, is a province in the Philippines located on", "expected": " Samar Island in Eastern Visayas. Its capital is Catbalogan City. It is bordered by Northern Samar, Eastern", "actual": " the west coast of Panay. It consists of the municipalities of San Fernando, San Mariano, Sagua, Santa Cruz, Santa Rosa, and Santa María while the Capital (town) of the province is San Fernando (town).\n\nSamar has a land area of 1,099,000 square kilometers and its population at the 2010 Census was 6,664,567 comprising the provinces and municipalities of Camarines Sur and Oriental Mindoro in the North, Northern Samar Island and Samar, a number equivalent to that of all the provinces of the country.\n\nHistory\nSamar is inhabited"}
{"prompt": "Tracheobronchopathia osteochondroplastica: a rare cause of difficult intubation.\nTr", "expected": "acheobronchopathia osteochondroplastica is a rare benign airway disorder which is characterised by sub", "actual": "acheobronchopathia osteochondroplastica (TO) is a rare benign idiopathic proliferative tracheobronchial disease involving the cartilage, ligament, muscle, and bone. It is typically diagnosed at an early age. This condition can cause life-threatening airway obstruction and is a diagnostic dilemma for the critical care setting. TO can present with laryngeal cartilage or cricoid paralysis. Difficult airway management can be achieved with direct laryngoscopy, video laryngoscopy (VLS), or a tracheal tube inserted via"}
{"prompt": "Such was the number and variety of responses to this challenge that presenting a detailed breakdown of one such solution – as has been the", "expected": " case for all of the first eleven in this series of challenges – would, I feel, be somewhat inappropriate.\n\nFor", "actual": " case with the various different proposals on the table, none of which is perfect (in my view, at least), to me, at this point seems an over-simplification, an unnecessary indulgence, and an unfortunate distraction from the main point – which will be argued in the next instalment of the series of articles.\n\nTo be honest, I’ve been a little puzzled by the number of ‘solutions’ proposed (or, more properly, the lack of solutions). I find it difficult to imagine a system more suited to my personal needs – for it to be simple, in"}
{"prompt": "longdesc_tr=Komutları aynı anda birden çok sunucuda ç", "expected": "alıştırın.\ndesc_tr=Küme Kabuğu Komutları", "actual": "alıştırılabilir.\nlongdesc_trs=Aynı anda birden çok sunucuda çalıştırılabilir.\nmore_like_this_title=Açarsanız\nmore_like_this_desc=Açarsanız, birden çok sunucu için kullanıldı\nmore_likes_this_title=Açarsanız\nmore_likes_this_desc=Açarsanız,"}
{"prompt": "/**\n * @license\n * Blockly Tests\n *\n * Copyright 2012 Google Inc.\n * https://developers", "expected": ".google.com/blockly/\n *\n * Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"", "actual": ".google.com/blockly/\n *\n * Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");\n * you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n * You may obtain a copy of the License at\n *\n *   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n *\n * Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n * distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,\n * WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either"}
{"prompt": "Paula Reid, Nicole Sganga and Steven Portnoy contributed to this report\n\nPaul Manafort, President Trump's", "expected": " former campaign chairman, has been found guilty on five counts of tax fraud, one count of failing to disclose his foreign bank accounts", "actual": " former campaign chairman, arrives at court on charges he faces in Washington on July 21, 2017. (Jabin Botsford/The Washington Post)\n\nThe Trump campaign was run by a crew that was in love with America, and this love is exactly what led a grand jury to indict 12 Russians, six of whom were campaign officials.\n\nOn that point, we can all agree.\n\nManafort may have made off with the $10,000 per month he collected from the Trump Organization. But he also took the money for himself and the businesses, in effect becoming the president's private moneyman.\n"}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\npulling a random item from multiple arrays\n\nI have 12 arrays named f1 to f12 each", "expected": " with five items. I want to randomly pull one item from each array and push these into the new array sm1.\n", "actual": " with 100 items in them.  I would like to pull a certain item, but only if there is enough room in my list.\nWhat is the best way to go about this?\nvar items=[];\nfor (var i=0;i<100;i++){\n    items.push(i);\n}\n\nvar f1=new Array(items.length);\nfor (var i=0;i<100;i++){\n    f1+=items[i];\n}\n\nvar f2=new Array(items.length);\n"}
{"prompt": "更新\n\n東京都は７日、昨年�", "expected": "��０～１１月に舛添要一", "actual": "監禁など計３千人以上の被害者がひとりで死亡した精病病院などの医療機関を約２％削減すると発表した。白砂症（３２）という高血圧現象症"}
{"prompt": "Sujata Koirala Daughter’s Big Fat ‘Illegal’ Wedding Mocks Nepali Law\n", "expected": "\nNepal Army Chief Pyar Jung Thapa (extreme right, with Nepali cap) along with Mrs. Th", "actual": "\nSujata Koirala has defended her daughter’s “illegitimate” wedding by arguing that Nepal’s constitution does not recognize same-sex marriages.\n\nShare This Article\n\nThis is an archived article and the information in the article may be outdated. Please look at the time stamp on the story to see when it was last updated.\n\nMUMBAI– As Nepal is struggling to address its increasing number of LGBT Nepalis, the daughter of the country’s late Prime Minister has come to the rescue by defending her right to a lesbian wedding.\n\n"}
{"prompt": "\"Dr. Draper and her staff have been amazing! I feel extremely comfortable with both of them which makes me more comfortable with", "expected": " her. She is a beautiful professional lady so initially I was a little bit intimidated but at my 2nd appointment which was my", "actual": " the procedure as well as the entire team at The Center.\" ~Liz\n\nWe are proud to provide quality and affordable cosmetic and surgical procedures for women in California. Our experienced, passionate and compassionate medical staff will listen to your concerns and concerns our staff will be with you every step of the way."}
{"prompt": "The Joker Deluxe Adult Latex Mask\n\nBatman is sure to come after you this Halloween when you put on this Deluxe J", "expected": "oke Latex Mask for adults. Terrorize Gotham City and put fear in the hearts of its civilians! As the Joker,", "actual": "okers mask. You’ll get a whole set of your choice of facial expressions and then some. It’s as easy to use as it is to look good in it. It’s made of 100% pure latex, so you won’t come across a single bit of air or other toxins. But the best-selling Latex masks on the market don’t just look great, they last you through several Halloween nights in the comfort of your own skin without needing to reapply.\n\nLatex masks are often made with a lot of hard and sharp edges that could get into"}
{"prompt": "In order to increase the available interior space of a motorized or towable vehicle such as a motor home or trailer, slide", "expected": "-out rooms can be made integral with the vehicle. When the vehicle is in transit, the slide-out room can be", "actual": " mechanisms are often provided for the rear doors leading into or out of the interior space. Typically, such slide mechanisms are located within the door panels of the doors, and generally include a slide rail, or track, fixedly mounted in one or more wall panels of the vehicle, with the slide rails generally in the form of rails that are parallel to the floor of the vehicle with the rail end portions abutting against one another in the door panel. The slide rails are movable along the track between a vertical retracted position and a deployed position in which the interior of the vehicle is open. The slide rail end portions generally extend"}
{"prompt": "I'm switching ecommerce platforms today, so ordering will be restored in 2 hours.\n\nIs posting the link to it", "expected": " against the ATS terms? If so, I'd be happy to send you a message with a link.\n\nI", "actual": " here likely to get me banned from this site (if I'm banned, there's a good chance I'll go elsewhere to avoid the temptation and then get banned)?\n\nI don't think they would be banned because they didn't do anything illegal but they could come under FTC scrutiny for what has come under my eyes. I'm not sure what they did that got me so curious.\n\nI don't think they would be banned because they didn't do anything illegal but they could come under FTC scrutiny for what has come under my eyes.\n\nClick to expand...\n\nSo it is clear that you are"}
{"prompt": "EVERYDAY CARRY (EDC)\n\nFEATURED USER PROFILE\n\nA KEY HOL", "expected": "DER, KEY ORGANIZER, & MULTI-TOOL\n\nNot Just a Premium Key Holder or Compact", "actual": "DER\n\nFor more than 25 years I have been creating content on a wide array of topics. From cooking to fitness to life in general, my goal is to deliver entertaining and informative content that is useful to my audience. My approach is to always find and provide interesting content so that any reader seeking some good reading material will click through.\n\nI have created my own website at www.dailycarry.com, which features my current book title, “THE WORLD’S MOST ADDICTING SHOPPING BAG” as well as a collection of articles. I also maintain a website that"}
{"prompt": "“So many people on this block alone that I know that have lost their homes, lost everything. This is bad,", "expected": "” Michael Sullivan said.\n\nDavid Klippel, 78, a retired police officer, said he didn’", "actual": "” Linn said, in tears.\n\nWith help from fellow activists, she organized the block party outside a bar and grill on E St. in the River North neighborhood to raise awareness about the problems facing the South Side. At the party, she asked neighbors and passers-by for their stories about the crime, drugs and violence on the block.\n\n\"When I was in Chicago, I was like, 'Why is everything so bad here?' But when I am in Washington, I could see why you have to be on constant alert,\" said Linn.\n\nAs she looked up, she said"}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThe present invention relates to a mobile terminal having an antenna transmitting and receiving radio electromagnetic waves.", "expected": "\n2. Description of the Related Art\nTerminals may be divided into a mobile/portable terminal and a stationary terminal", "actual": " More particularly, the present invention relates to an antenna device capable of reducing a size, a cost, a manufacturing process, a wireless module and a mounting method used in a mobile terminal having an antenna transmitting and receiving radio electromagnetic waves.\n2. Description of the Related Art\nGenerally, terminals can be divided into mobile terminals and stationary terminals according to whether they are installed in vehicles or not, and also divided into handheld terminals and vehicle mount terminals according to whether they can be carried by a user.\nAs the functions of the terminal are diversified, the terminal is implemented as a multimedia player having multiple functions such as capturing pictures"}
{"prompt": "/* Declarations for getopt.\n   Copyright 1989, 1990, 1991, 1992, 1993, 1994, 1996,", "expected": " 1997, 1998, 2000,\n   2002 Free Software Foundation, Inc.\n\n   NOTE: The canonical source of", "actual": " 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000,\n   2001, 2002, 2016 Free Software Foundation, Inc.\n\n   This file is part of the GNU MP Library.\n\n   The GNU MP Library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify\n   it under the terms of either:\n\n     * the GNU Lesser General Public License as published by the Free\n       Software Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your\n       option) any later version.\n\n   or\n\n   "}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nUsing DateTime in Livecharts WPF\n\nI have created a CartesianChart using LiveCh", "expected": "arts in WPF which shows values from a list called NIOquoteTrend. The list is populated with values from a database", "actual": "arts, but I don't know how to add Dates.\nI want to start my \"X\" Axis at 2018-01-12 00:00:00 and end it in 2022-01-12 00:00:00.\nHere is my code, maybe its too verbose for you :\n<local:ChartsPanel Orientation=\"Vertical\" Grid.Column=\"1\" Grid.Row=\"1\"\n    Height=\"400\" Margin=\"10\" VerticalAlignment=\"Top\" DataContext=\"{StaticResource ResourceKey CartesianChart}\">\n    <local"}
{"prompt": "Beautiful Taormina Hotel Room\n\nEach room of Villa Angela is filled with an authentic Sicilian atmosphere, in perfect", "expected": " harmony with the fascinating dimensions of the location. With chestnut and wrought iron furniture, the rooms of this striking hotel in Ta", "actual": " harmony with the character of the ancient and magnificent landscape.\n\nThe hotel features a beautiful garden and a large terrace overlooking the sea. The swimming pool with its swimming and sunbeds for rent can be enjoyed by guests after a long day of sightseeing.\n\nThe hotel’s restaurant “La Cucina” has a charming atmosphere, where the waiters are always friendly and efficient. The menu includes a wide choice of fresh local and regional dishes prepared with the highest quality products, such as fish and meat dishes.\n\nThe hotel’s bar “Nuova Salute"}
{"prompt": "./test/relaxng/list.rng validates\n", "expected": "", "actual": "       * lists with relaxNG\n       */\n      valid: !data.test.list\n    }\n  };\n\n\n  /*\n   * Tests and sample data\n   */\n  tests.index = function() {\n    return new TestCase(testRelaxNG(), testRelaxNGRegExp());\n  };\n\n  tests.list = function() {\n    return new TestCase(testRelaxNGRegExp(), testRelaxNG(), testRelaxNG());\n  };\n\n  tests.compare ="}
{"prompt": "DCE-MRI (dynamic contrast enhanced magnetic resonance imaging) is a physiologic MRI technique that quantifies perfusion (", "expected": "or permeability) in a target tissue. However, due to the variability in quantitative perfusion parameters across MR imaging platforms,", "actual": "a surrogate for cellularity) and permeability (a proxy for vascular density) parameters through the use of paramagnetic contrast agents.[@b1] The sensitivity of dynamic contrast enhanced (DCE)-MRI enables the visualization of in vivo dynamic pharmacokinetic (PK) parameters (eg, kinetics) of contrast enhancement and tissue vascularity in response to exogenously administered contrast agents. Using DCE-MRI, one can non-invasively and repeatedly measure contrast agent distribution and the kinetics of contrast agent clearance by calculating DCE-MR kinetics (DCE-MRK).\n\nDCE-"}
{"prompt": "Survivor's James Clement attends the 2010 CBS UpFront at Damrosch Park, Lincoln...Survivor's James", "expected": " Clement attends the 2010 CBS UpFront at Damrosch Park, Lincoln Center on May 19, 2010 in New York City.", "actual": " Clement attends the 2010 CBS UpFront at Damrosch Park, Lincoln Park,...\n\nSurvivor: David vs. Goliath, an upcoming CBS reality television series, will air a 90-day, three-episode series of its own on Sept. 20, according to a source.\n\nShowtime, the home of the boxing and reality series, already has a reality series in the works called Top Rank: Goliath — a similar concept with the show’s title and time frame.\n\nIf the Goliath show does begin, it would mark the first time in broadcast television history that a network"}
{"prompt": "Christian Living\n\nThirty Days of Excellence, contains some of the most powerful principles of excellence in Scripture and will encourage you to", "expected": " cultivate one principle of excellence into the soil of your life each day for the next thirty days.\n\nThirty Days of Excellence", "actual": " walk in the Spirit, to do the work God has for you, and to be ready to return to Him at any moment you don’t like what He is doing.\n\nHow to Use Thirty Days\n\nGod created you and has placed you in a special role, not only in your family, but also in the church. You are His child and are uniquely designed to live a life of excellence. Your relationship with Him will be enhanced if you live your life in accordance with these principles:\n\n1. Never make excuses.\n\nGod is a God of “No” and His �"}
{"prompt": "Last season, Phil Hughes set the record for the highest strikeout-to-walk ratio ever in MLB history. For months", "expected": ", baseball fans tried to figure out why -- his 11.63 K:BB ratio seemed superhuman, somehow. Magical, almost", "actual": " afterward, he was asked why that ratio was higher than ever before in his career. He had a simple answer: he was throwing from hell.\n\nAfter a spring in which he threw more swings and misses than hits, he started to think his first season as a starter was over and he would end up in Triple-A before he could even start his next season. Then, suddenly, it was over in the blink of an eye. After only two more full seasons in the Majors, he was called up by the Dodgers on Thursday to pitch against the San Diego Padres, starting Friday against the Diamondbacks. On"}
{"prompt": "Elk Lake Township, Grant County, Minnesota\n\nElk Lake Township is a township in Grant County, Minnesota, United", "expected": " States. The population was 298 at the 2000 census.\n\nElk Lake Township was organized in 1876, and named", "actual": " States. The population was 566 at the 2010 census.\n\nElk Lake Township was organized in 1868. Elk Lake Township, in turn, is one of two township sub-divisions of the city of Grant, the county seat of Grant County.\n\nElk Lake Township is named for Elk Lake, a small lake south of Lake Vermilion and near the site of the county's first court house. Elk Lake Township borders Elk Lake Township, North Lake Township, Vermilion Township, and West Lake Township.\n\nName\nThe first recorded name of \"Elk Lake Township\" was \""}
{"prompt": "122 F.3d 1067\nWestv.Texas Board of Pardons*\nNO. 97-50604", "expected": "\nUnited States Court of Appeals,Fifth Circuit.\nJuly 29, 1997\n\n1\nAppeal From: ", "actual": "\nUnited States Court of Appeals,Fifth Circuit.\nOct 16, 1997\n\n1\nAppeal From:  S.D.Tex. , No. SA-95-CA-049-F\n\n\n2\nDISMISSED.\n\n\n\n*\n Fed.R.App.P. 34(a); 5th Cir.R. 34-2\n\n\n"}
{"prompt": "169 F.3d 951\nIn The Matter Of:  MEDWAY RANCH, INC., also known as", "expected": " MedwayRanch, Debtor.Beal Bank, S.S.B., Appellant,v.Med", "actual": "The Medway Hotel;  Medway Corporation, Appellants,v.UNITED STATES VIRGIN ISLANDS BOARD OF HEALTH;  Dr. DonaldL. Lillis, Appellees.\nNo. 97-6171SI.\nUnited States Court of Appeals,Third Circuit.\nArgued Sept. 23, 1998.Decided Nov. 27, 1998.\n\nAndrew J. Lattas (argued), Lattas, Lattas & Lattas, Christiansted, St. Croix, USVI, for Appellants.\nJohn K"}
{"prompt": "Campground Reviews\n\nOct 22, 2013\n\nOct 22, 2013\n\nWe found the hills a bit daunting for", "expected": " our 40' coach + tow car. The park was very quiet and the staff very friendly. We enjoyed our stay and are", "actual": " our 4 kids, so we decided to take the easy way out by reserving for the week and coming down on Sunday. We were greeted at the park by an older gentleman named Mr. J., who was very friendly and showed us where everything was. We got into a cabin and had everything we needed. The cabin itself was very nice, even though the outside looked a little worn, and the interior was very clean. The toilet and shower was a little small but it worked out fine.\nWhen we got to the campground, we saw a group of about 15 people just leaving. We walked to this group and"}
{"prompt": "New Giants\n\nThis episode focuses on the new giants, the heavyweights of the dinosaur world. It is only in recent", "expected": " years that experts have unearthed the biggest dinosaurs that ever lived.\n\nOne monster, the immense argentinosaurus, eclips", "actual": " years that scientists have been able to accurately reconstruct dinosaur sizes, and thus it was no surprise when when I was looking for a new dinosaur to research, that I picked the recently discovered T. Rex. I began by looking at the largest ever discovered, the T. Rex at the U.S. National Museum of Natural History in Washington D.C. When I saw its size I couldn’t help but wonder how long it had lived and if it was truly a real dinosaur. It was clear that as I looked closer, my eyes had caught hints of what it might have been.\n\nI learned about the"}
{"prompt": "Once again it’s post-holiday ramble time, a chance to unwind, relax and enjoy the outdoors with", "expected": " nothing nagging you but the need to be where the wild things are.\nMost folks don’t stop to think", "actual": " some great reading. Enjoy my picks for December 31st, when I hope you can spend some time relaxing and taking it easy. Remember to use this post to plan your perfect day. This post does not have a link to any other post.\n\nHere are my December picks for some great outdoor reading:\n\nThe Secret Life of Walter Mitty by Walter Mosley\n\nWalter Mitty is the name given to a real life secret agent who goes undercover as a farmer near Santa Barbara, California. The premise is a fun read about a man who does ‘good’ deeds for a living, including"}
{"prompt": "1. Field of the Invention\nThis invention relates to appliances and, more particularly, to a vent assembly for controllably", "expected": " discharging combustion gases generated through operation of these appliances.\n2. Background Art\nMany different vent assemblies currently exist for contro", "actual": " removing air from a container and a process for controllably removing air from a container.\n2. Description of the Prior Art\nMany refrigerated containers have a dispensing mechanism for spraying an aerosol product into the air when a dispensing tap is activated, whether the dispense is via manual valve or mechanical valve controlled by electrical solenoids. When a dispensing tap is activated, the pressure within the container must be either maintained above atmospheric pressure or removed from the container.\nThe present invention is directed toward a vent assembly that is particularly useful for dispensing products, such as aerosol sprays, from a"}
{"prompt": "#include <arpa/inet.h>\n\n#include <gmock/gmock.h>\n\n", "expected": "#include <netinet/in.h>\n#include <netinet/tcp.h>\n\n#", "actual": "\nclass MockSmbClient : public SmbClient\n{\n  public:\n    template <typename T>\n    MOCK_METHOD0(Connect, void(T* client, uint16_t connection_id));\n    MOCK_METHOD0(ConnectEx, void(T* client, uint16_t connection_id));\n\n    template <class S, class T>\n    MOCK_METHOD1(Connect, void(S* client, T* server));\n};\n\n\n// ************************************************************************** //\n\n"}
{"prompt": "Former Premier League referee Howard Webb reveals huge mistake in Tottenham game\n\nFormer referee Howard Webb has revealed that the decision he regrets", "expected": " most in career was awarding Manchester United a controversial penalty during a Premier League game against Tottenham in the 2008/2009 campaign.\n", "actual": " most from Premier League games is the decision to award Spurs a penalty against Newcastle at White Hart Lane on 25 November 2012.\n\nWebb said that Tottenham's goal was “a ridiculous goal” that was a “total waste of time” but that the Newcastle goal was “despicable” and “a disgrace”.\n\nWebb was given the benefit of the doubt after a controversial decision which could have meant a goal being awarded for the first time in Tottenham's history.\n\nBut Webb said that he regrets the decision for the rest of his life - even if he"}
{"prompt": "Introduction {#s1}\n============\n\nDiabetes is a major risk factor for atherosclerosis, which predisposes", "expected": " patients to occlusive coronary artery disease (CAD), acute myocardial infarction (AMI), and death [", "actual": " cardiovascular disease (CVD) [@pone.0069084-Westerbeek1]--[@pone.0069084-Papassotiropoulos1]. The aorta is a major target for CVD, with CVD accounts for more than 65% of deaths in individuals with diabetes [@pone.0069084-Westerbeek1]--[@pone.0069084-Papassotiropoulos1]. Atherosclerosis, especially in the aorta, causes thickening and stiffening of the vessel wall."}
{"prompt": "Q:\n\nAsk for recommendations for textbook on mathematical logic\n\nI studied mathematical logic using a book not written in English", "expected": ". I would now like to study it again using a textbook in English. But I hope I can read a text that is", "actual": " (the book I read was by K.Kaminski, \"An Introduction to Mathematical Logic\"). \nI learned the language in the book but I still can't speak and write Polish. And I would like to know if it is possible to ask for recommendations for a second language text that focuses on mathematical logic (without the term \"mathematical logic\"), for example, a text written in any other language than English.\n\nA:\n\nYou can get a good introduction to the theory of the formal language by reading\nW. Ewald, An Introduction to Symbolic Logic. \nThis book"}
{"prompt": "Evaluation of cell subpopulations isolated from human tumor xenografts by centrifugal elutriation.\n", "expected": "Human epidermoid tumor cells (Coll2, ME180, A431, HEp3) grown as xenog", "actual": "We have fractionated human tumor xenografts from the NCI-60 cell line panel into non-tumoral (NTC) and tumor cell (TC) subpopulations by centrifugal elutriation. The NTC subpopulation was depleted of cells with elevated levels of surface antigens and was enriched for cells expressing stem cell-specific markers. The TC subpopulation was distinguished by its ability to form tumors in NOD/SCID mice and by its expression of cell surface markers commonly associated with cancer progenitor cells. Characterization of the TC fraction on the basis of differential attachment to tissue"}
{"prompt": "George Chaump\n\nGeorge Chaump (April 28, 1936 – May 19, 2019) was an American football player and", "expected": " coach. He served as head coach at Indiana University of Pennsylvania (1982–1985), Marshall University (1986–1989), and", "actual": " end.  He played college football at the University of Illinois, and was selected by the Associated Press and United Press International as a first-team player on the College Football All-America Team in 1956. Chaump was the first African-American to coach a high school team in the state of Illinois.\n\nAfter the end of his active football career, Chaump served as the defensive coordinator at the University of California, Berkeley, where he was the first African-American named head coach of a major collegiate football program.\n\nFollowing his time with the NFL's Oakland Raiders, Chaump served as an assistant coach for"}
{"prompt": "Newsletters\n\nget the best of where we live\n\nSent to Your Inbox", "expected": "", "actual": "\n\nShare with friends\n\nabout us and our partner brands\n\nWe're a little bit different in that, since we're not based in New York, we don't have to have the typical morning coffee on the East Village stoop. Our coffee is served all day to our guests--and to anyone who cares to stop by our little bistro at any time.\n\nOur cafe has an upstairs loft space designed to showcase vintage glass. Our kitchen is an open concept, and so we serve breakfast from the first moment you walk in our door.\n\nWe are now part of the new neighborhood of Greenpoint and are opening our storefront"}
{"prompt": "Open Workbench\n\nOpen Workbench is a free project management software focused on scheduling. It is an alternative to Microsoft Project", "expected": ".\n\nHistory\nOpen Workbench was originally (1984) developed by Christopher H. Murray and Danek M. B", "actual": " which can be used for any application that wants to use a simple graphical user interface.\n\nHistory \nIn the late 1990s, the German company Pallas, in partnership with the University of Bielefeld, developed a software product named Open Project, which eventually changed its name to Project Management Open Workbench. The name Open Workbench was chosen to emphasize that the system supports \"Open Source\" projects. The software is open source and the source code for the software projects that have been developed using the software can be viewed by others.\n\nThe name Open Workbench is short for the Open Project management software,"}
{"prompt": "Introduction {#Sec1}\n============\n\nThe Pleistocene megafauna of Sahul are defined here as non", "expected": "-marine vertebrates that exceed a mass of \\~40--44 kg^[@CR1]^,", "actual": "-historic vertebrates that were present in the Southern Hemisphere during the Late Pleistocene. Megafauna refers to large animals that are typically characterized by an ecological role that cannot be fulfilled by small mammals \\[[@CR33]\\]. In this review we refer to marine megafauna because it is a unique and complex group in the context of modern and ancient marine ecosystems \\[[@CR33], [@CR46]\\]. They are considered to be representative examples of the evolution of modern marine megafauna \\[[@CR33]\\].\n\nWhile marine megafauna are known for both marine and"}
{"prompt": "Six in seven households have received some sort of government benefit, according to a new survey from Pew Research Center. Here are some", "expected": " highlights from the report, plus some extra bits of context. These graphs focus on government spending, as opposed to tax benefits --", "actual": " of the most generous recipients of government aid.\n\nWASHINGTON — The federal government is providing financial help for millions of low-income Americans, and these are its top recipients.\n\nThe number of Americans receiving government aid hit a record high of 6 in 7 in the new survey, released Thursday. That figure is up from 6 in 10 in 2011 as federal aid rose by 17.5 percent, totaling $1.47 trillion.\n\n\nPew’s survey, called the Annual Census of Aid to Families with Dependent Children, was based on interviews by telephone with 3,002 households in the month following July"}
{"prompt": "1991–92 Iraq FA Cup\n\nThe 1991–92 Iraq FA Cup was the 15th edition of the Iraq FA Cup", "expected": ". The tournament was won by Al-Quwa Al-Jawiya for the second time in their history, beating Al", "actual": ".\nThe Cup started on 2 September 1991.\n\nIt was competed by all Iraq clubs, which had competed in the 1990–91 Gulf Cup Winners Cup.\n\nThe final was played between Al-Quwa Al-Jawiya and Al-Talaba at the Al-Najma Stadium on 30 November. Al-Quwa won the cup for the second time with a 2–0 win.\n\nIt was the last time Al-Quwa Al-Jawiya was successful in a cup competition.\n\nFirst round\n\nReplays\n\nSecond round\n\nReplays\n\n"}
